Rank,Title,Genre,Description,Director,Actors,Year,Runtime (Minutes),Rating,Votes,Revenue (Millions),Metascore,entities
1,Guardians of the Galaxy,"Action,Adventure,Sci-Fi",A group of intergalactic criminals are forced to work together to stop a fanatical warrior from taking control of the universe.,James Gunn,"Chris Pratt, Vin Diesel, Bradley Cooper, Zoe Saldana",2014,121,8.1,757074,333.13,76,"[{'start': 11, 'end': 34, 'text': 'intergalactic criminals', 'label': 'character', 'score': 0.5833504796028137}, {'start': 73, 'end': 90, 'text': 'fanatical warrior', 'label': 'character', 'score': 0.9020678997039795}, {'start': 118, 'end': 126, 'text': 'universe', 'label': 'location', 'score': 0.8479593396186829}]"
2,Prometheus,"Adventure,Mystery,Sci-Fi","Following clues to the origin of mankind, a team finds a structure on a distant moon, but they soon realize they are not alone.",Ridley Scott,"Noomi Rapace, Logan Marshall-Green, Michael Fassbender, Charlize Theron",2012,124,7.0,485820,126.46,65,"[{'start': 80, 'end': 84, 'text': 'moon', 'label': 'location', 'score': 0.9769169688224792}]"
3,Split,"Horror,Thriller",Three girls are kidnapped by a man with a diagnosed 23 distinct personalities. They must try to escape before the apparent emergence of a frightful new 24th.,M. Night Shyamalan,"James McAvoy, Anya Taylor-Joy, Haley Lu Richardson, Jessica Sula",2016,117,7.3,157606,138.12,62,"[{'start': 0, 'end': 11, 'text': 'Three girls', 'label': 'person', 'score': 0.5702298283576965}, {'start': 31, 'end': 34, 'text': 'man', 'label': 'person', 'score': 0.9494022727012634}, {'start': 152, 'end': 156, 'text': '24th', 'label': 'date', 'score': 0.7765721678733826}]"
4,Sing,"Animation,Comedy,Family","In a city of humanoid animals, a hustling theater impresario's attempt to save his theater with a singing competition becomes grander than he anticipates even as its finalists' find that their lives will never be the same.",Christophe Lourdelet,"Matthew McConaughey,Reese Witherspoon, Seth MacFarlane, Scarlett Johansson",2016,108,7.2,60545,270.32,59,"[{'start': 5, 'end': 29, 'text': 'city of humanoid animals', 'label': 'location', 'score': 0.9306044578552246}, {'start': 33, 'end': 60, 'text': 'hustling theater impresario', 'label': 'person', 'score': 0.8813484907150269}, {'start': 166, 'end': 175, 'text': 'finalists', 'label': 'person', 'score': 0.5973895788192749}]"
5,Suicide Squad,"Action,Adventure,Fantasy",A secret government agency recruits some of the most dangerous incarcerated super-villains to form a defensive task force. Their first mission: save the world from the apocalypse.,David Ayer,"Will Smith, Jared Leto, Margot Robbie, Viola Davis",2016,123,6.2,393727,325.02,40,"[{'start': 0, 'end': 26, 'text': 'A secret government agency', 'label': 'location', 'score': 0.47719234228134155}, {'start': 76, 'end': 90, 'text': 'super-villains', 'label': 'character', 'score': 0.694063127040863}, {'start': 153, 'end': 158, 'text': 'world', 'label': 'location', 'score': 0.8731613755226135}]"
6,The Great Wall,"Action,Adventure,Fantasy",European mercenaries searching for black powder become embroiled in the defense of the Great Wall of China against a horde of monstrous creatures.,Yimou Zhang,"Matt Damon, Tian Jing, Willem Dafoe, Andy Lau",2016,103,6.1,56036,45.13,42,"[{'start': 87, 'end': 106, 'text': 'Great Wall of China', 'label': 'location', 'score': 0.9868248105049133}]"
7,La La Land,"Comedy,Drama,Music",A jazz pianist falls for an aspiring actress in Los Angeles.,Damien Chazelle,"Ryan Gosling, Emma Stone, Rosemarie DeWitt, J.K. Simmons",2016,128,8.3,258682,151.06,93,"[{'start': 2, 'end': 14, 'text': 'jazz pianist', 'label': 'person', 'score': 0.9326391816139221}, {'start': 28, 'end': 44, 'text': 'aspiring actress', 'label': 'actor', 'score': 0.8655943274497986}, {'start': 48, 'end': 59, 'text': 'Los Angeles', 'label': 'location', 'score': 0.9936936497688293}]"
8,Mindhorn,Comedy,"A has-been actor best known for playing the title character in the 1980s detective series ""Mindhorn"" must work with the police when a serial killer says that he will only speak with Detective Mindhorn, whom he believes to be a real person.",Sean Foley,"Essie Davis, Andrea Riseborough, Julian Barratt,Kenneth Branagh",2016,89,6.4,2490,0.0,71,"[{'start': 0, 'end': 16, 'text': 'A has-been actor', 'label': 'actor', 'score': 0.5089609026908875}, {'start': 91, 'end': 99, 'text': 'Mindhorn', 'label': 'character', 'score': 0.9729376435279846}, {'start': 134, 'end': 147, 'text': 'serial killer', 'label': 'person', 'score': 0.608363151550293}, {'start': 192, 'end': 200, 'text': 'Mindhorn', 'label': 'character', 'score': 0.9284145832061768}]"
9,The Lost City of Z,"Action,Adventure,Biography","A true-life drama, centering on British explorer Col. Percival Fawcett, who disappeared while searching for a mysterious city in the Amazon in the 1920s.",James Gray,"Charlie Hunnam, Robert Pattinson, Sienna Miller, Tom Holland",2016,141,7.1,7188,8.01,78,"[{'start': 32, 'end': 48, 'text': 'British explorer', 'label': 'person', 'score': 0.6101722717285156}, {'start': 49, 'end': 70, 'text': 'Col. Percival Fawcett', 'label': 'person', 'score': 0.9798005819320679}, {'start': 133, 'end': 139, 'text': 'Amazon', 'label': 'location', 'score': 0.9778494834899902}]"
10,Passengers,"Adventure,Drama,Romance","A spacecraft traveling to a distant colony planet and transporting thousands of people has a malfunction in its sleep chambers. As a result, two passengers are awakened 90 years early.",Morten Tyldum,"Jennifer Lawrence, Chris Pratt, Michael Sheen,Laurence Fishburne",2016,116,7.0,192177,100.01,41,"[{'start': 0, 'end': 12, 'text': 'A spacecraft', 'label': 'location', 'score': 0.5361809730529785}, {'start': 36, 'end': 49, 'text': 'colony planet', 'label': 'location', 'score': 0.9511623382568359}]"
11,Fantastic Beasts and Where to Find Them,"Adventure,Family,Fantasy",The adventures of writer Newt Scamander in New York's secret community of witches and wizards seventy years before Harry Potter reads his book in school.,David Yates,"Eddie Redmayne, Katherine Waterston, Alison Sudol,Dan Fogler",2016,133,7.5,232072,234.02,66,"[{'start': 25, 'end': 39, 'text': 'Newt Scamander', 'label': 'character', 'score': 0.9755800366401672}, {'start': 43, 'end': 51, 'text': 'New York', 'label': 'location', 'score': 0.9739974141120911}, {'start': 115, 'end': 127, 'text': 'Harry Potter', 'label': 'character', 'score': 0.9855808615684509}]"
12,Hidden Figures,"Biography,Drama,History",The story of a team of female African-American mathematicians who served a vital role in NASA during the early years of the U.S. space program.,Theodore Melfi,"Taraji P. Henson, Octavia Spencer, Janelle Monáe,Kevin Costner",2016,127,7.8,93103,169.27,74,"[{'start': 89, 'end': 93, 'text': 'NASA', 'label': 'location', 'score': 0.6920523643493652}, {'start': 124, 'end': 142, 'text': 'U.S. space program', 'label': 'location', 'score': 0.6478774547576904}]"
13,Rogue One,"Action,Adventure,Sci-Fi","The Rebel Alliance makes a risky move to steal the plans for the Death Star, setting up the epic saga to follow.",Gareth Edwards,"Felicity Jones, Diego Luna, Alan Tudyk, Donnie Yen",2016,133,7.9,323118,532.17,65,"[{'start': 4, 'end': 18, 'text': 'Rebel Alliance', 'label': 'location', 'score': 0.5881507396697998}, {'start': 65, 'end': 75, 'text': 'Death Star', 'label': 'location', 'score': 0.9547645449638367}, {'start': 92, 'end': 101, 'text': 'epic saga', 'label': 'book', 'score': 0.6444303393363953}]"
14,Moana,"Animation,Adventure,Comedy","In Ancient Polynesia, when a terrible curse incurred by the Demigod Maui reaches an impetuous Chieftain's daughter's island, she answers the Ocean's call to seek out the Demigod to set things right.",Ron Clements,"Auli'i Cravalho, Dwayne Johnson, Rachel House, Temuera Morrison",2016,107,7.7,118151,248.75,81,"[{'start': 3, 'end': 20, 'text': 'Ancient Polynesia', 'label': 'location', 'score': 0.8686855435371399}, {'start': 60, 'end': 72, 'text': 'Demigod Maui', 'label': 'character', 'score': 0.9074912071228027}, {'start': 94, 'end': 103, 'text': 'Chieftain', 'label': 'person', 'score': 0.9573851823806763}, {'start': 106, 'end': 114, 'text': 'daughter', 'label': 'person', 'score': 0.7969059348106384}, {'start': 117, 'end': 123, 'text': 'island', 'label': 'location', 'score': 0.7624632120132446}, {'start': 141, 'end': 146, 'text': 'Ocean', 'label': 'location', 'score': 0.6004987955093384}, {'start': 170, 'end': 177, 'text': 'Demigod', 'label': 'character', 'score': 0.6310831904411316}]"
15,Colossal,"Action,Comedy,Drama","Gloria is an out-of-work party girl forced to leave her life in New York City, and move back home. When reports surface that a giant creature is destroying Seoul, she gradually comes to the realization that she is somehow connected to this phenomenon.",Nacho Vigalondo,"Anne Hathaway, Jason Sudeikis, Austin Stowell,Tim Blake Nelson",2016,109,6.4,8612,2.87,70,"[{'start': 64, 'end': 77, 'text': 'New York City', 'label': 'location', 'score': 0.9982359409332275}, {'start': 156, 'end': 161, 'text': 'Seoul', 'label': 'location', 'score': 0.9973322153091431}]"
16,The Secret Life of Pets,"Animation,Adventure,Comedy","The quiet life of a terrier named Max is upended when his owner takes in Duke, a stray whom Max instantly dislikes.",Chris Renaud,"Louis C.K., Eric Stonestreet, Kevin Hart, Lake Bell",2016,87,6.6,120259,368.31,61,"[{'start': 34, 'end': 37, 'text': 'Max', 'label': 'character', 'score': 0.9983311295509338}, {'start': 58, 'end': 63, 'text': 'owner', 'label': 'person', 'score': 0.6524122357368469}, {'start': 73, 'end': 77, 'text': 'Duke', 'label': 'character', 'score': 0.994172990322113}, {'start': 92, 'end': 95, 'text': 'Max', 'label': 'character', 'score': 0.9980658888816833}]"
17,Hacksaw Ridge,"Biography,Drama,History","WWII American Army Medic Desmond T. Doss, who served during the Battle of Okinawa, refuses to kill people, and becomes the first man in American history to receive the Medal of Honor without firing a shot.",Mel Gibson,"Andrew Garfield, Sam Worthington, Luke Bracey,Teresa Palmer",2016,139,8.2,211760,67.12,71,"[{'start': 25, 'end': 40, 'text': 'Desmond T. Doss', 'label': 'person', 'score': 0.9926267266273499}, {'start': 74, 'end': 81, 'text': 'Okinawa', 'label': 'location', 'score': 0.9680967926979065}]"
18,Jason Bourne,"Action,Thriller",The CIA's most dangerous former operative is drawn out of hiding to uncover more explosive truths about his past.,Paul Greengrass,"Matt Damon, Tommy Lee Jones, Alicia Vikander,Vincent Cassel",2016,123,6.7,150823,162.16,58,"[{'start': 0, 'end': 3, 'text': 'The', 'label': '', 'score': 0.5437203645706177}, {'start': 4, 'end': 7, 'text': 'CIA', 'label': 'location', 'score': 0.8037137389183044}, {'start': 25, 'end': 41, 'text': 'former operative', 'label': 'character', 'score': 0.5717190504074097}]"
19,Lion,"Biography,Drama","A five-year-old Indian boy gets lost on the streets of Calcutta, thousands of kilometers from home. He survives many challenges before being adopted by a couple in Australia. 25 years later, he sets out to find his lost family.",Garth Davis,"Dev Patel, Nicole Kidman, Rooney Mara, Sunny Pawar",2016,118,8.1,102061,51.69,69,"[{'start': 16, 'end': 26, 'text': 'Indian boy', 'label': 'person', 'score': 0.7840477824211121}, {'start': 55, 'end': 63, 'text': 'Calcutta', 'label': 'location', 'score': 0.9983240962028503}, {'start': 164, 'end': 173, 'text': 'Australia', 'label': 'location', 'score': 0.9979357719421387}]"
20,Arrival,"Drama,Mystery,Sci-Fi","When twelve mysterious spacecraft appear around the world, linguistics professor Louise Banks is tasked with interpreting the language of the apparent alien visitors.",Denis Villeneuve,"Amy Adams, Jeremy Renner, Forest Whitaker,Michael Stuhlbarg",2016,116,8.0,340798,100.5,81,"[{'start': 52, 'end': 57, 'text': 'world', 'label': 'location', 'score': 0.7710371613502502}, {'start': 81, 'end': 93, 'text': 'Louise Banks', 'label': 'person', 'score': 0.9913890957832336}, {'start': 151, 'end': 165, 'text': 'alien visitors', 'label': 'book', 'score': 0.4466720223426819}]"
21,Gold,"Adventure,Drama,Thriller","Kenny Wells, a prospector desperate for a lucky break, teams up with a similarly eager geologist and sets off on a journey to find gold in the uncharted jungle of Indonesia.",Stephen Gaghan,"Matthew McConaughey, Edgar Ramírez, Bryce Dallas Howard, Corey Stoll",2016,120,6.7,19053,7.22,49,"[{'start': 0, 'end': 11, 'text': 'Kenny Wells', 'label': 'person', 'score': 0.6323565244674683}, {'start': 15, 'end': 25, 'text': 'prospector', 'label': 'person', 'score': 0.4583052694797516}, {'start': 87, 'end': 96, 'text': 'geologist', 'label': 'person', 'score': 0.7908097505569458}, {'start': 163, 'end': 172, 'text': 'Indonesia', 'label': 'location', 'score': 0.9955050945281982}]"
22,Manchester by the Sea,Drama,A depressed uncle is asked to take care of his teenage nephew after the boy's father dies.,Kenneth Lonergan,"Casey Affleck, Michelle Williams, Kyle Chandler,Lucas Hedges",2016,137,7.9,134213,47.7,96,"[{'start': 0, 'end': 1, 'text': 'A', 'label': 'person', 'score': 0.5059312582015991}, {'start': 12, 'end': 17, 'text': 'uncle', 'label': 'person', 'score': 0.9672434329986572}, {'start': 47, 'end': 61, 'text': 'teenage nephew', 'label': 'person', 'score': 0.916998028755188}, {'start': 72, 'end': 75, 'text': 'boy', 'label': 'person', 'score': 0.7258515357971191}, {'start': 78, 'end': 84, 'text': 'father', 'label': 'person', 'score': 0.9611932039260864}]"
23,Hounds of Love,"Crime,Drama,Horror","A cold-blooded predatory couple while cruising the streets in search of their next victim, will stumble upon a 17-year-old high school girl, who will be sedated, abducted and chained in the strangers' guest room.",Ben Young,"Emma Booth, Ashleigh Cummings, Stephen Curry,Susie Porter",2016,108,6.7,1115,0.0,72,"[{'start': 111, 'end': 139, 'text': '17-year-old high school girl', 'label': 'person', 'score': 0.893446147441864}, {'start': 190, 'end': 199, 'text': 'strangers', 'label': 'person', 'score': 0.7666563391685486}, {'start': 201, 'end': 211, 'text': 'guest room', 'label': 'location', 'score': 0.9439674019813538}]"
24,Trolls,"Animation,Adventure,Comedy","After the Bergens invade Troll Village, Poppy, the happiest Troll ever born, and the curmudgeonly Branch set off on a journey to rescue her friends.",Walt Dohrn,"Anna Kendrick, Justin Timberlake,Zooey Deschanel, Christopher Mintz-Plasse",2016,92,6.5,38552,153.69,56,"[{'start': 10, 'end': 17, 'text': 'Bergens', 'label': '', 'score': 0.5379601716995239}, {'start': 25, 'end': 38, 'text': 'Troll Village', 'label': 'location', 'score': 0.9908961653709412}, {'start': 40, 'end': 45, 'text': 'Poppy', 'label': 'character', 'score': 0.9946684241294861}, {'start': 98, 'end': 104, 'text': 'Branch', 'label': 'character', 'score': 0.9835288524627686}]"
25,Independence Day: Resurgence,"Action,Adventure,Sci-Fi","Two decades after the first Independence Day invasion, Earth is faced with a new extra-Solar threat. But will mankind's new space defenses be enough?",Roland Emmerich,"Liam Hemsworth, Jeff Goldblum, Bill Pullman,Maika Monroe",2016,120,5.3,127553,103.14,32,"[{'start': 28, 'end': 44, 'text': 'Independence Day', 'label': 'movie', 'score': 0.7571942806243896}, {'start': 55, 'end': 60, 'text': 'Earth', 'label': 'location', 'score': 0.9890815019607544}, {'start': 81, 'end': 92, 'text': 'extra-Solar', 'label': 'location', 'score': 0.6860451102256775}, {'start': 110, 'end': 117, 'text': 'mankind', 'label': 'location', 'score': 0.5135738253593445}]"
26,Paris pieds nus,Comedy,"Fiona visits Paris for the first time to assist her myopic Aunt Martha. Catastrophes ensue, mainly involving Dom, a homeless man who has yet to have an emotion or thought he was afraid of expressing.",Dominique Abel,"Fiona Gordon, Dominique Abel,Emmanuelle Riva, Pierre Richard",2016,83,6.8,222,0.0,61,"[{'start': 13, 'end': 18, 'text': 'Paris', 'label': 'location', 'score': 0.9983102083206177}, {'start': 59, 'end': 70, 'text': 'Aunt Martha', 'label': 'person', 'score': 0.9513075351715088}, {'start': 109, 'end': 112, 'text': 'Dom', 'label': 'person', 'score': 0.9625333547592163}]"
27,Bahubali: The Beginning,"Action,Adventure,Drama","In ancient India, an adventurous and daring man becomes involved in a decades old feud between two warring people.",S.S. Rajamouli,"Prabhas, Rana Daggubati, Anushka Shetty,Tamannaah Bhatia",2015,159,8.3,76193,6.5,45,"[{'start': 11, 'end': 16, 'text': 'India', 'label': 'location', 'score': 0.9543552398681641}, {'start': 44, 'end': 47, 'text': 'man', 'label': 'person', 'score': 0.8529969453811646}]"
28,Dead Awake,"Horror,Thriller",A young woman must save herself and her friends from an ancient evil that stalks its victims through the real-life phenomenon of sleep paralysis.,Phillip Guzman,"Jocelin Donahue, Jesse Bradford, Jesse Borrego,Lori Petty",2016,99,4.7,523,0.01,34,"[{'start': 2, 'end': 13, 'text': 'young woman', 'label': 'person', 'score': 0.8204129338264465}, {'start': 56, 'end': 68, 'text': 'ancient evil', 'label': '', 'score': 0.5228306651115417}]"
29,Bad Moms,Comedy,"When three overworked and under-appreciated moms are pushed beyond their limits, they ditch their conventional responsibilities for a jolt of long overdue freedom, fun, and comedic self-indulgence.",Jon Lucas,"Mila Kunis, Kathryn Hahn, Kristen Bell,Christina Applegate",2016,100,6.2,66540,113.08,60,"[{'start': 0, 'end': 4, 'text': 'When', 'label': '', 'score': 0.4687243700027466}, {'start': 44, 'end': 48, 'text': 'moms', 'label': 'person', 'score': 0.6951794624328613}]"
30,Assassin's Creed,"Action,Adventure,Drama","When Callum Lynch explores the memories of his ancestor Aguilar and gains the skills of a Master Assassin, he discovers he is a descendant of the secret Assassins society.",Justin Kurzel,"Michael Fassbender, Marion Cotillard, Jeremy Irons,Brendan Gleeson",2016,115,5.9,112813,54.65,36,"[{'start': 5, 'end': 17, 'text': 'Callum Lynch', 'label': 'character', 'score': 0.9927765130996704}, {'start': 56, 'end': 63, 'text': 'Aguilar', 'label': 'person', 'score': 0.9887669682502747}, {'start': 90, 'end': 105, 'text': 'Master Assassin', 'label': 'person', 'score': 0.4827726185321808}]"
31,Why Him?,Comedy,A holiday gathering threatens to go off the rails when Ned Fleming realizes that his daughter's Silicon Valley millionaire boyfriend is about to pop the question.,John Hamburg,"Zoey Deutch, James Franco, Tangie Ambrose,Cedric the Entertainer",2016,111,6.3,48123,60.31,39,"[{'start': 55, 'end': 66, 'text': 'Ned Fleming', 'label': 'character', 'score': 0.9882053136825562}, {'start': 96, 'end': 110, 'text': 'Silicon Valley', 'label': 'location', 'score': 0.9905154705047607}, {'start': 111, 'end': 132, 'text': 'millionaire boyfriend', 'label': 'person', 'score': 0.5353567004203796}]"
32,Nocturnal Animals,"Drama,Thriller","A wealthy art gallery owner is haunted by her ex-husband's novel, a violent thriller she interprets as a symbolic revenge tale.",Tom Ford,"Amy Adams, Jake Gyllenhaal, Michael Shannon, Aaron Taylor-Johnson",2016,116,7.5,126030,10.64,67,"[{'start': 0, 'end': 27, 'text': 'A wealthy art gallery owner', 'label': 'character', 'score': 0.5906365513801575}, {'start': 46, 'end': 56, 'text': 'ex-husband', 'label': 'person', 'score': 0.8932176232337952}, {'start': 59, 'end': 64, 'text': 'novel', 'label': 'book', 'score': 0.8015406131744385}, {'start': 68, 'end': 84, 'text': 'violent thriller', 'label': 'book', 'score': 0.6303556561470032}, {'start': 114, 'end': 126, 'text': 'revenge tale', 'label': 'book', 'score': 0.47232332825660706}]"
33,X-Men: Apocalypse,"Action,Adventure,Sci-Fi","After the re-emergence of the world's first mutant, world-destroyer Apocalypse, the X-Men must unite to defeat his extinction level plan.",Bryan Singer,"James McAvoy, Michael Fassbender, Jennifer Lawrence, Nicholas Hoult",2016,144,7.1,275510,155.33,52,"[{'start': 30, 'end': 35, 'text': 'world', 'label': 'location', 'score': 0.7035164833068848}, {'start': 68, 'end': 78, 'text': 'Apocalypse', 'label': 'character', 'score': 0.9896292090415955}, {'start': 84, 'end': 89, 'text': 'X-Men', 'label': 'character', 'score': 0.5471887588500977}]"
34,Deadpool,"Action,Adventure,Comedy",A fast-talking mercenary with a morbid sense of humor is subjected to a rogue experiment that leaves him with accelerated healing powers and a quest for revenge.,Tim Miller,"Ryan Reynolds, Morena Baccarin, T.J. Miller, Ed Skrein",2016,108,8.0,627797,363.02,65,"[{'start': 0, 'end': 1, 'text': 'A', 'label': '', 'score': 0.40134626626968384}, {'start': 15, 'end': 24, 'text': 'mercenary', 'label': 'character', 'score': 0.89057457447052}, {'start': 32, 'end': 53, 'text': 'morbid sense of humor', 'label': 'character', 'score': 0.5084786415100098}]"
35,Resident Evil: The Final Chapter,"Action,Horror,Sci-Fi","Alice returns to where the nightmare began: The Hive in Raccoon City, where the Umbrella Corporation is gathering its forces for a final strike against the only remaining survivors of the apocalypse.",Paul W.S. Anderson,"Milla Jovovich, Iain Glen, Ali Larter, Shawn Roberts",2016,107,5.6,46165,26.84,49,"[{'start': 44, 'end': 52, 'text': 'The Hive', 'label': 'location', 'score': 0.9797084927558899}, {'start': 56, 'end': 68, 'text': 'Raccoon City', 'label': 'location', 'score': 0.9937781095504761}, {'start': 80, 'end': 100, 'text': 'Umbrella Corporation', 'label': 'location', 'score': 0.9601037502288818}]"
36,Captain America: Civil War,"Action,Adventure,Sci-Fi",Political interference in the Avengers' activities causes a rift between former allies Captain America and Iron Man.,Anthony Russo,"Chris Evans, Robert Downey Jr.,Scarlett Johansson, Sebastian Stan",2016,147,7.9,411656,408.08,75,"[{'start': 30, 'end': 38, 'text': 'Avengers', 'label': 'location', 'score': 0.5511366128921509}, {'start': 87, 'end': 102, 'text': 'Captain America', 'label': 'character', 'score': 0.9985896944999695}, {'start': 107, 'end': 115, 'text': 'Iron Man', 'label': 'character', 'score': 0.9984360337257385}]"
37,Interstellar,"Adventure,Drama,Sci-Fi",A team of explorers travel through a wormhole in space in an attempt to ensure humanity's survival.,Christopher Nolan,"Matthew McConaughey, Anne Hathaway, Jessica Chastain, Mackenzie Foy",2014,169,8.6,1047747,187.99,74,"[{'start': 0, 'end': 19, 'text': 'A team of explorers', 'label': 'person', 'score': 0.4384838938713074}, {'start': 37, 'end': 45, 'text': 'wormhole', 'label': 'location', 'score': 0.8509533405303955}, {'start': 49, 'end': 54, 'text': 'space', 'label': 'location', 'score': 0.8969630002975464}, {'start': 79, 'end': 87, 'text': 'humanity', 'label': 'location', 'score': 0.9032738208770752}]"
38,Doctor Strange,"Action,Adventure,Fantasy","While on a journey of physical and spiritual healing, a brilliant neurosurgeon is drawn into the world of the mystic arts.",Scott Derrickson,"Benedict Cumberbatch, Chiwetel Ejiofor, Rachel McAdams, Benedict Wong",2016,115,7.6,293732,232.6,72,"[{'start': 66, 'end': 78, 'text': 'neurosurgeon', 'label': 'person', 'score': 0.8443334102630615}, {'start': 110, 'end': 121, 'text': 'mystic arts', 'label': 'location', 'score': 0.8261063098907471}]"
39,The Magnificent Seven,"Action,Adventure,Western",Seven gunmen in the old west gradually come together to help a poor village against savage thieves.,Antoine Fuqua,"Denzel Washington, Chris Pratt, Ethan Hawke,Vincent D'Onofrio",2016,132,6.9,122853,93.38,54,"[{'start': 0, 'end': 12, 'text': 'Seven gunmen', 'label': 'person', 'score': 0.6358699798583984}, {'start': 20, 'end': 28, 'text': 'old west', 'label': 'location', 'score': 0.9618820548057556}, {'start': 63, 'end': 75, 'text': 'poor village', 'label': 'location', 'score': 0.9352823495864868}, {'start': 84, 'end': 98, 'text': 'savage thieves', 'label': 'person', 'score': 0.6202760338783264}]"
40,5/25/1977,"Comedy,Drama","Alienated, hopeful-filmmaker Pat Johnson's epic story growing up in rural Illinois, falling in love, and becoming the first fan of the movie that changed everything.",Patrick Read Johnson,"John Francis Daley, Austin Pendleton, Colleen Camp, Neil Flynn",2007,113,7.1,241,0.0,71,"[{'start': 11, 'end': 28, 'text': 'hopeful-filmmaker', 'label': 'character', 'score': 0.4389563500881195}, {'start': 29, 'end': 40, 'text': 'Pat Johnson', 'label': 'character', 'score': 0.9197471141815186}, {'start': 74, 'end': 82, 'text': 'Illinois', 'label': 'location', 'score': 0.916816234588623}, {'start': 135, 'end': 164, 'text': 'movie that changed everything', 'label': 'movie', 'score': 0.7533060312271118}]"
41,Sausage Party,"Animation,Adventure,Comedy",A sausage strives to discover the truth about his existence.,Greg Tiernan,"Seth Rogen, Kristen Wiig, Jonah Hill, Alistair Abell",2016,89,6.3,120690,97.66,66,"[{'start': 0, 'end': 1, 'text': 'A', 'label': 'character', 'score': 0.48738616704940796}, {'start': 2, 'end': 9, 'text': 'sausage', 'label': 'character', 'score': 0.7995065450668335}]"
42,Moonlight,Drama,"A chronicle of the childhood, adolescence and burgeoning adulthood of a young, African-American, gay man growing up in a rough neighborhood of Miami.",Barry Jenkins,"Mahershala Ali, Shariff Earp, Duan Sanderson, Alex R. Hibbert",2016,111,7.5,135095,27.85,99,"[{'start': 143, 'end': 148, 'text': 'Miami', 'label': 'location', 'score': 0.9430810809135437}]"
43,Don't Fuck in the Woods,Horror,"A group of friends are going on a camping trip to celebrate graduating college. But once they enter the woods, the proverbial shit starts to hit the fan.",Shawn Burkett,"Brittany Blanton, Ayse Howard, Roman Jossart,Nadia White",2016,73,2.7,496,0.0,64,"[{'start': 0, 'end': 18, 'text': 'A group of friends', 'label': 'person', 'score': 0.4677758812904358}, {'start': 71, 'end': 78, 'text': 'college', 'label': 'location', 'score': 0.4248806834220886}, {'start': 104, 'end': 109, 'text': 'woods', 'label': 'location', 'score': 0.9290526509284973}]"
44,The Founder,"Biography,Drama,History","The story of Ray Kroc, a salesman who turned two brothers' innovative fast food eatery, McDonald's, into one of the biggest restaurant businesses in the world with a combination of ambition, persistence, and ruthlessness.",John Lee Hancock,"Michael Keaton, Nick Offerman, John Carroll Lynch, Linda Cardellini",2016,115,7.2,37033,12.79,66,"[{'start': 13, 'end': 21, 'text': 'Ray Kroc', 'label': 'person', 'score': 0.9942439198493958}, {'start': 88, 'end': 98, 'text': ""McDonald's"", 'label': 'location', 'score': 0.7213744521141052}]"
45,Lowriders,Drama,"A young street artist in East Los Angeles is caught between his father's obsession with lowrider car culture, his ex-felon brother and his need for self-expression.",Ricardo de Montreuil,"Gabriel Chavarria, Demián Bichir, Theo Rossi,Tony Revolori",2016,99,6.3,279,4.21,57,"[{'start': 0, 'end': 21, 'text': 'A young street artist', 'label': 'person', 'score': 0.7308298945426941}, {'start': 25, 'end': 41, 'text': 'East Los Angeles', 'label': 'location', 'score': 0.9900051951408386}, {'start': 64, 'end': 70, 'text': 'father', 'label': 'person', 'score': 0.9427881240844727}, {'start': 114, 'end': 130, 'text': 'ex-felon brother', 'label': 'person', 'score': 0.9399276375770569}]"
46,Pirates of the Caribbean: On Stranger Tides,"Action,Adventure,Fantasy","Jack Sparrow and Barbossa embark on a quest to find the elusive fountain of youth, only to discover that Blackbeard and his daughter are after it too.",Rob Marshall,"Johnny Depp, Penélope Cruz, Ian McShane, Geoffrey Rush",2011,136,6.7,395025,241.06,45,"[{'start': 0, 'end': 12, 'text': 'Jack Sparrow', 'label': 'character', 'score': 0.5219385027885437}, {'start': 17, 'end': 25, 'text': 'Barbossa', 'label': 'character', 'score': 0.9955463409423828}, {'start': 64, 'end': 81, 'text': 'fountain of youth', 'label': 'location', 'score': 0.9057724475860596}, {'start': 105, 'end': 115, 'text': 'Blackbeard', 'label': 'person', 'score': 0.959152102470398}]"
47,Miss Sloane,"Drama,Thriller","In the high-stakes world of political power-brokers, Elizabeth Sloane is the most sought after and formidable lobbyist in D.C. But when taking on the most powerful opponent of her career, she finds winning may come at too high a price.",John Madden,"Jessica Chastain, Mark Strong, Gugu Mbatha-Raw,Michael Stuhlbarg",2016,132,7.3,17818,3.44,64,"[{'start': 53, 'end': 69, 'text': 'Elizabeth Sloane', 'label': 'person', 'score': 0.9810189008712769}, {'start': 122, 'end': 126, 'text': 'D.C.', 'label': 'location', 'score': 0.9762609601020813}]"
48,Fallen,"Adventure,Drama,Fantasy","A young girl finds herself in a reform school after therapy since she was blamed for the death of a young boy. At the school she finds herself drawn to a fellow student, unaware that he is an angel, and has loved her for thousands of years.",Scott Hicks,"Hermione Corfield, Addison Timlin, Joely Richardson,Jeremy Irvine",2016,91,5.6,5103,0.0,52,"[{'start': 2, 'end': 12, 'text': 'young girl', 'label': 'person', 'score': 0.9035060405731201}, {'start': 32, 'end': 45, 'text': 'reform school', 'label': 'location', 'score': 0.9773066639900208}, {'start': 100, 'end': 109, 'text': 'young boy', 'label': 'person', 'score': 0.9229474067687988}, {'start': 154, 'end': 168, 'text': 'fellow student', 'label': 'person', 'score': 0.8301497101783752}, {'start': 192, 'end': 197, 'text': 'angel', 'label': 'character', 'score': 0.9286140203475952}]"
49,Star Trek Beyond,"Action,Adventure,Sci-Fi","The USS Enterprise crew explores the furthest reaches of uncharted space, where they encounter a new ruthless enemy who puts them and everything the Federation stands for to the test.",Justin Lin,"Chris Pine, Zachary Quinto, Karl Urban, Zoe Saldana",2016,122,7.1,164567,158.8,68,"[{'start': 4, 'end': 18, 'text': 'USS Enterprise', 'label': 'location', 'score': 0.7977173924446106}, {'start': 57, 'end': 72, 'text': 'uncharted space', 'label': 'location', 'score': 0.9653960466384888}, {'start': 101, 'end': 115, 'text': 'ruthless enemy', 'label': 'character', 'score': 0.5612972974777222}, {'start': 149, 'end': 159, 'text': 'Federation', 'label': 'location', 'score': 0.7107937335968018}]"
50,The Last Face,Drama,"A director (Charlize Theron) of an international aid agency in Africa meets a relief aid doctor (Javier Bardem) amidst a political/social revolution, and together face tough choices ... See full summary »",Sean Penn,"Charlize Theron, Javier Bardem, Adèle Exarchopoulos,Jared Harris",2016,130,3.7,987,0.0,16,"[{'start': 0, 'end': 1, 'text': 'A', 'label': 'character', 'score': 0.45764869451522827}, {'start': 2, 'end': 10, 'text': 'director', 'label': 'character', 'score': 0.6779834032058716}, {'start': 12, 'end': 27, 'text': 'Charlize Theron', 'label': 'actor', 'score': 0.996475875377655}, {'start': 63, 'end': 69, 'text': 'Africa', 'label': 'location', 'score': 0.971024751663208}, {'start': 78, 'end': 95, 'text': 'relief aid doctor', 'label': 'character', 'score': 0.7244365811347961}, {'start': 97, 'end': 110, 'text': 'Javier Bardem', 'label': 'actor', 'score': 0.9986584186553955}]"
51,Star Wars: Episode VII - The Force Awakens,"Action,Adventure,Fantasy","Three decades after the defeat of the Galactic Empire, a new threat arises. The First Order attempts to rule the galaxy and only a ragtag group of heroes can stop them, along with the help of the Resistance.",J.J. Abrams,"Daisy Ridley, John Boyega, Oscar Isaac, Domhnall Gleeson",2015,136,8.1,661608,936.63,81,"[{'start': 38, 'end': 53, 'text': 'Galactic Empire', 'label': 'location', 'score': 0.7900113463401794}, {'start': 80, 'end': 91, 'text': 'First Order', 'label': 'location', 'score': 0.5831541419029236}, {'start': 113, 'end': 119, 'text': 'galaxy', 'label': 'location', 'score': 0.782645583152771}, {'start': 196, 'end': 206, 'text': 'Resistance', 'label': '', 'score': 0.4622669219970703}]"
52,Underworld: Blood Wars,"Action,Adventure,Fantasy","Vampire death dealer, Selene (Kate Beckinsale) fights to end the eternal war between the Lycan clan and the Vampire faction that betrayed her.",Anna Foerster,"Kate Beckinsale, Theo James, Tobias Menzies, Lara Pulver",2016,91,5.8,41362,30.35,23,"[{'start': 22, 'end': 28, 'text': 'Selene', 'label': 'character', 'score': 0.9962049126625061}, {'start': 30, 'end': 45, 'text': 'Kate Beckinsale', 'label': 'actor', 'score': 0.998975396156311}, {'start': 89, 'end': 99, 'text': 'Lycan clan', 'label': 'location', 'score': 0.7616749405860901}, {'start': 108, 'end': 123, 'text': 'Vampire faction', 'label': 'location', 'score': 0.6345645189285278}]"
53,Mother's Day,"Comedy,Drama",Three generations come together in the week leading up to Mother's Day.,Garry Marshall,"Jennifer Aniston, Kate Hudson, Julia Roberts, Jason Sudeikis",2016,118,5.6,20221,32.46,18,"[{'start': 58, 'end': 64, 'text': 'Mother', 'label': 'person', 'score': 0.7252542972564697}]"
54,John Wick,"Action,Crime,Thriller",An ex-hitman comes out of retirement to track down the gangsters that took everything from him.,Chad Stahelski,"Keanu Reeves, Michael Nyqvist, Alfie Allen, Willem Dafoe",2014,101,7.2,321933,43.0,68,"[{'start': 0, 'end': 2, 'text': 'An', 'label': 'person', 'score': 0.5320332646369934}, {'start': 3, 'end': 12, 'text': 'ex-hitman', 'label': 'person', 'score': 0.8829779028892517}, {'start': 55, 'end': 64, 'text': 'gangsters', 'label': 'location', 'score': 0.6763251423835754}]"
55,The Dark Knight,"Action,Crime,Drama","When the menace known as the Joker wreaks havoc and chaos on the people of Gotham, the Dark Knight must come to terms with one of the greatest psychological tests of his ability to fight injustice.",Christopher Nolan,"Christian Bale, Heath Ledger, Aaron Eckhart,Michael Caine",2008,152,9.0,1791916,533.32,82,"[{'start': 29, 'end': 34, 'text': 'Joker', 'label': 'person', 'score': 0.8632826209068298}, {'start': 75, 'end': 81, 'text': 'Gotham', 'label': 'location', 'score': 0.9934052228927612}, {'start': 87, 'end': 98, 'text': 'Dark Knight', 'label': 'character', 'score': 0.9911893606185913}]"
56,Silence,"Adventure,Drama,History","In the 17th century, two Portuguese Jesuit priests travel to Japan in an attempt to locate their mentor, who is rumored to have committed apostasy, and to propagate Catholicism.",Martin Scorsese,"Andrew Garfield, Adam Driver, Liam Neeson,Tadanobu Asano",2016,161,7.3,49190,7.08,79,"[{'start': 7, 'end': 19, 'text': '17th century', 'label': 'date', 'score': 0.7935407161712646}, {'start': 25, 'end': 50, 'text': 'Portuguese Jesuit priests', 'label': 'person', 'score': 0.8228790760040283}, {'start': 61, 'end': 66, 'text': 'Japan', 'label': 'location', 'score': 0.9944764971733093}, {'start': 97, 'end': 103, 'text': 'mentor', 'label': 'person', 'score': 0.47568732500076294}]"
57,Don't Breathe,"Crime,Horror,Thriller","Hoping to walk away with a massive fortune, a trio of thieves break into the house of a blind man who isn't as helpless as he seems.",Fede Alvarez,"Stephen Lang, Jane Levy, Dylan Minnette, Daniel Zovatto",2016,88,7.2,121103,89.21,71,"[{'start': 46, 'end': 61, 'text': 'trio of thieves', 'label': 'character', 'score': 0.8875329494476318}, {'start': 77, 'end': 82, 'text': 'house', 'label': 'location', 'score': 0.7804011702537537}, {'start': 88, 'end': 97, 'text': 'blind man', 'label': 'person', 'score': 0.9397740364074707}]"
58,Me Before You,"Drama,Romance",A girl in a small town forms an unlikely bond with a recently-paralyzed man she's taking care of.,Thea Sharrock,"Emilia Clarke, Sam Claflin, Janet McTeer, Charles Dance",2016,106,7.4,113322,56.23,51,"[{'start': 0, 'end': 1, 'text': 'A', 'label': 'person', 'score': 0.6157253980636597}, {'start': 2, 'end': 6, 'text': 'girl', 'label': 'person', 'score': 0.9223936796188354}, {'start': 12, 'end': 22, 'text': 'small town', 'label': 'location', 'score': 0.967373788356781}, {'start': 72, 'end': 75, 'text': 'man', 'label': 'person', 'score': 0.8107902407646179}]"
59,Their Finest,"Comedy,Drama,Romance","A former secretary, newly appointed as a scriptwriter for propaganda films, joins the cast and crew of a major production while the Blitz rages around them.",Lone Scherfig,"Gemma Arterton, Sam Claflin, Bill Nighy, Jack Huston",2016,117,7.0,3739,3.18,76,"[{'start': 2, 'end': 18, 'text': 'former secretary', 'label': 'person', 'score': 0.8212756514549255}, {'start': 41, 'end': 53, 'text': 'scriptwriter', 'label': 'person', 'score': 0.6087446212768555}, {'start': 58, 'end': 74, 'text': 'propaganda films', 'label': 'movie', 'score': 0.9692633748054504}, {'start': 105, 'end': 121, 'text': 'major production', 'label': 'location', 'score': 0.4798070192337036}, {'start': 132, 'end': 137, 'text': 'Blitz', 'label': 'location', 'score': 0.8059281706809998}]"
60,Sully,"Biography,Drama","The story of Chesley Sullenberger, an American pilot who became a hero after landing his damaged plane on the Hudson River in order to save the flight's passengers and crew.",Clint Eastwood,"Tom Hanks, Aaron Eckhart, Laura Linney, Valerie Mahaffey",2016,96,7.5,137608,125.07,74,"[{'start': 13, 'end': 33, 'text': 'Chesley Sullenberger', 'label': 'person', 'score': 0.9895491600036621}, {'start': 110, 'end': 122, 'text': 'Hudson River', 'label': 'location', 'score': 0.987341582775116}]"
61,Batman v Superman: Dawn of Justice,"Action,Adventure,Sci-Fi","Fearing that the actions of Superman are left unchecked, Batman takes on the Man of Steel, while the world wrestles with what kind of a hero it really needs.",Zack Snyder,"Ben Affleck, Henry Cavill, Amy Adams, Jesse Eisenberg",2016,151,6.7,472307,330.25,44,"[{'start': 28, 'end': 36, 'text': 'Superman', 'label': 'character', 'score': 0.9963164329528809}, {'start': 57, 'end': 63, 'text': 'Batman', 'label': 'character', 'score': 0.995884358882904}, {'start': 77, 'end': 89, 'text': 'Man of Steel', 'label': 'character', 'score': 0.9775356650352478}, {'start': 101, 'end': 106, 'text': 'world', 'label': 'location', 'score': 0.8208145499229431}]"
62,The Autopsy of Jane Doe,"Horror,Mystery,Thriller","A father and son, both coroners, are pulled into a complex mystery while attempting to identify the body of a young woman, who was apparently harboring dark secrets.",André Øvredal,"Brian Cox, Emile Hirsch, Ophelia Lovibond, Michael McElhatton",2016,86,6.8,35870,0.0,65,"[{'start': 0, 'end': 1, 'text': 'A', 'label': 'person', 'score': 0.5586284399032593}, {'start': 2, 'end': 8, 'text': 'father', 'label': 'person', 'score': 0.9227935671806335}, {'start': 13, 'end': 16, 'text': 'son', 'label': 'person', 'score': 0.8763829469680786}, {'start': 23, 'end': 31, 'text': 'coroners', 'label': 'person', 'score': 0.6899372935295105}, {'start': 110, 'end': 121, 'text': 'young woman', 'label': 'person', 'score': 0.9636684656143188}]"
63,The Girl on the Train,"Crime,Drama,Mystery",A divorcee becomes entangled in a missing persons investigation that promises to send shockwaves throughout her life.,Tate Taylor,"Emily Blunt, Haley Bennett, Rebecca Ferguson, Justin Theroux",2016,112,6.5,102177,75.31,48,"[{'start': 0, 'end': 1, 'text': 'A', 'label': 'person', 'score': 0.5186494588851929}, {'start': 2, 'end': 10, 'text': 'divorcee', 'label': 'person', 'score': 0.8855354189872742}, {'start': 34, 'end': 63, 'text': 'missing persons investigation', 'label': 'location', 'score': 0.40814030170440674}]"
64,Fifty Shades of Grey,"Drama,Romance,Thriller","Literature student Anastasia Steele's life changes forever when she meets handsome, yet tormented, billionaire Christian Grey.",Sam Taylor-Johnson,"Dakota Johnson, Jamie Dornan, Jennifer Ehle,Eloise Mumford",2015,125,4.1,244474,166.15,46,"[{'start': 19, 'end': 35, 'text': 'Anastasia Steele', 'label': 'character', 'score': 0.9958032965660095}, {'start': 111, 'end': 125, 'text': 'Christian Grey', 'label': 'person', 'score': 0.9531718492507935}]"
65,The Prestige,"Drama,Mystery,Sci-Fi",Two stage magicians engage in competitive one-upmanship in an attempt to create the ultimate stage illusion.,Christopher Nolan,"Christian Bale, Hugh Jackman, Scarlett Johansson, Michael Caine",2006,130,8.5,913152,53.08,66,"[{'start': 0, 'end': 19, 'text': 'Two stage magicians', 'label': 'person', 'score': 0.648489236831665}]"
66,Kingsman: The Secret Service,"Action,Adventure,Comedy","A spy organization recruits an unrefined, but promising street kid into the agency's ultra-competitive training program, just as a global threat emerges from a twisted tech genius.",Matthew Vaughn,"Colin Firth, Taron Egerton, Samuel L. Jackson,Michael Caine",2014,129,7.7,440209,128.25,58,"[{'start': 2, 'end': 18, 'text': 'spy organization', 'label': 'location', 'score': 0.5486456155776978}, {'start': 56, 'end': 66, 'text': 'street kid', 'label': 'person', 'score': 0.9052111506462097}, {'start': 160, 'end': 179, 'text': 'twisted tech genius', 'label': 'character', 'score': 0.8653496503829956}]"
67,Patriots Day,"Drama,History,Thriller","The story of the 2013 Boston Marathon bombing and the aftermath, which includes the city-wide manhunt to find the terrorists responsible.",Peter Berg,"Mark Wahlberg, Michelle Monaghan, J.K. Simmons, John Goodman",2016,133,7.4,39784,31.86,69,"[{'start': 17, 'end': 21, 'text': '2013', 'label': 'date', 'score': 0.40216708183288574}, {'start': 22, 'end': 37, 'text': 'Boston Marathon', 'label': 'location', 'score': 0.7404575943946838}, {'start': 84, 'end': 101, 'text': 'city-wide manhunt', 'label': 'location', 'score': 0.5432586669921875}]"
68,Mad Max: Fury Road,"Action,Adventure,Sci-Fi","A woman rebels against a tyrannical ruler in postapocalyptic Australia in search for her home-land with the help of a group of female prisoners, a psychotic worshipper, and a drifter named Max.",George Miller,"Tom Hardy, Charlize Theron, Nicholas Hoult, Zoë Kravitz",2015,120,8.1,632842,153.63,90,"[{'start': 0, 'end': 1, 'text': 'A', 'label': 'person', 'score': 0.5510630011558533}, {'start': 2, 'end': 7, 'text': 'woman', 'label': 'person', 'score': 0.8004060387611389}, {'start': 25, 'end': 41, 'text': 'tyrannical ruler', 'label': 'person', 'score': 0.7726014256477356}, {'start': 61, 'end': 70, 'text': 'Australia', 'label': 'location', 'score': 0.9643622040748596}, {'start': 89, 'end': 98, 'text': 'home-land', 'label': 'location', 'score': 0.42938724160194397}, {'start': 127, 'end': 143, 'text': 'female prisoners', 'label': 'character', 'score': 0.5322257876396179}, {'start': 147, 'end': 167, 'text': 'psychotic worshipper', 'label': 'character', 'score': 0.7418076992034912}, {'start': 175, 'end': 182, 'text': 'drifter', 'label': 'character', 'score': 0.6604453325271606}, {'start': 189, 'end': 192, 'text': 'Max', 'label': 'character', 'score': 0.9928117394447327}]"
69,Wakefield,Drama,A man's nervous breakdown causes him to leave his wife and live in his attic for several months.,Robin Swicord,"Bryan Cranston, Jennifer Garner, Beverly D'Angelo,Jason O'Mara",2016,106,7.5,291,0.01,61,"[{'start': 0, 'end': 1, 'text': 'A', 'label': 'person', 'score': 0.6208114624023438}, {'start': 2, 'end': 5, 'text': 'man', 'label': 'person', 'score': 0.944200336933136}, {'start': 50, 'end': 54, 'text': 'wife', 'label': 'person', 'score': 0.9110406637191772}, {'start': 71, 'end': 76, 'text': 'attic', 'label': 'location', 'score': 0.9259209036827087}]"
70,Deepwater Horizon,"Action,Drama,Thriller","A dramatization of the April 2010 disaster, when the offshore drilling rig Deepwater Horizon exploded and created the worst oil spill in U.S. history.",Peter Berg,"Mark Wahlberg, Kurt Russell, Douglas M. Griffin, James DuMont",2016,107,7.2,89849,61.28,68,"[{'start': 23, 'end': 33, 'text': 'April 2010', 'label': 'date', 'score': 0.838919460773468}, {'start': 75, 'end': 92, 'text': 'Deepwater Horizon', 'label': 'location', 'score': 0.9551213979721069}, {'start': 137, 'end': 141, 'text': 'U.S.', 'label': 'location', 'score': 0.8810615539550781}]"
71,The Promise,"Drama,History","Set during the last days of the Ottoman Empire, The Promise follows a love triangle between Michael, a brilliant medical student, the beautiful and sophisticated Ana, and Chris - a renowned American journalist based in Paris.",Terry George,"Oscar Isaac, Charlotte Le Bon, Christian Bale, Daniel Giménez Cacho",2016,133,5.9,149791,0.0,49,"[{'start': 32, 'end': 46, 'text': 'Ottoman Empire', 'label': 'location', 'score': 0.9169766902923584}, {'start': 48, 'end': 59, 'text': 'The Promise', 'label': 'movie', 'score': 0.987522542476654}, {'start': 92, 'end': 99, 'text': 'Michael', 'label': 'character', 'score': 0.9895586967468262}, {'start': 162, 'end': 165, 'text': 'Ana', 'label': 'character', 'score': 0.9930323362350464}, {'start': 171, 'end': 176, 'text': 'Chris', 'label': 'character', 'score': 0.9887092709541321}, {'start': 219, 'end': 224, 'text': 'Paris', 'label': 'location', 'score': 0.9851051568984985}]"
72,Allied,"Action,Drama,Romance","In 1942, a Canadian intelligence officer in North Africa encounters a female French Resistance fighter on a deadly mission behind enemy lines. When they reunite in London, their relationship is tested by the pressures of war.",Robert Zemeckis,"Brad Pitt, Marion Cotillard, Jared Harris, Vincent Ebrahim",2016,124,7.1,78079,40.07,60,"[{'start': 3, 'end': 7, 'text': '1942', 'label': 'date', 'score': 0.9880907535552979}, {'start': 11, 'end': 40, 'text': 'Canadian intelligence officer', 'label': 'person', 'score': 0.9499573707580566}, {'start': 44, 'end': 56, 'text': 'North Africa', 'label': 'location', 'score': 0.9979138970375061}, {'start': 77, 'end': 102, 'text': 'French Resistance fighter', 'label': 'person', 'score': 0.9408780336380005}, {'start': 164, 'end': 170, 'text': 'London', 'label': 'location', 'score': 0.9887545108795166}]"
73,A Monster Calls,"Drama,Fantasy",A boy seeks the help of a tree monster to cope with his single mother's terminal illness.,J.A. Bayona,"Lewis MacDougall, Sigourney Weaver, Felicity Jones,Toby Kebbell",2016,108,7.5,39134,3.73,76,"[{'start': 0, 'end': 1, 'text': 'A', 'label': 'person', 'score': 0.5743743181228638}, {'start': 2, 'end': 5, 'text': 'boy', 'label': 'person', 'score': 0.9200055599212646}, {'start': 26, 'end': 38, 'text': 'tree monster', 'label': 'character', 'score': 0.9800090789794922}, {'start': 56, 'end': 69, 'text': 'single mother', 'label': 'person', 'score': 0.9129043817520142}]"
74,Collateral Beauty,"Drama,Romance","Retreating from life after a tragedy, a man questions the universe by writing to Love, Time and Death. Receiving unexpected answers, he begins to see how these things interlock and how even loss can reveal moments of meaning and beauty.",David Frankel,"Will Smith, Edward Norton, Kate Winslet, Michael Peña",2016,97,6.8,43977,30.98,23,"[{'start': 40, 'end': 43, 'text': 'man', 'label': 'person', 'score': 0.8832772970199585}, {'start': 81, 'end': 101, 'text': 'Love, Time and Death', 'label': 'book', 'score': 0.9839441776275635}, {'start': 133, 'end': 135, 'text': 'he', 'label': 'person', 'score': 0.4005369544029236}]"
75,Zootopia,"Animation,Adventure,Comedy","In a city of anthropomorphic animals, a rookie bunny cop and a cynical con artist fox must work together to uncover a conspiracy.",Byron Howard,"Ginnifer Goodwin, Jason Bateman, Idris Elba, Jenny Slate",2016,108,8.1,296853,341.26,78,"[{'start': 5, 'end': 36, 'text': 'city of anthropomorphic animals', 'label': 'location', 'score': 0.9635103344917297}, {'start': 40, 'end': 56, 'text': 'rookie bunny cop', 'label': 'character', 'score': 0.9584611058235168}, {'start': 63, 'end': 85, 'text': 'cynical con artist fox', 'label': 'character', 'score': 0.9680169224739075}]"
76,Pirates of the Caribbean: At World's End,"Action,Adventure,Fantasy","Captain Barbossa, Will Turner and Elizabeth Swann must sail off the edge of the map, navigate treachery and betrayal, find Jack Sparrow, and make their final alliances for one last decisive battle.",Gore Verbinski,"Johnny Depp, Orlando Bloom, Keira Knightley,Geoffrey Rush",2007,169,7.1,498821,309.4,50,"[{'start': 0, 'end': 16, 'text': 'Captain Barbossa', 'label': 'character', 'score': 0.7776126265525818}, {'start': 18, 'end': 29, 'text': 'Will Turner', 'label': 'character', 'score': 0.9951533079147339}, {'start': 34, 'end': 49, 'text': 'Elizabeth Swann', 'label': 'character', 'score': 0.9890177249908447}, {'start': 123, 'end': 135, 'text': 'Jack Sparrow', 'label': 'character', 'score': 0.9951122403144836}]"
77,The Avengers,"Action,Sci-Fi",Earth's mightiest heroes must come together and learn to fight as a team if they are to stop the mischievous Loki and his alien army from enslaving humanity.,Joss Whedon,"Robert Downey Jr., Chris Evans, Scarlett Johansson,Jeremy Renner",2012,143,8.1,1045588,623.28,69,"[{'start': 109, 'end': 113, 'text': 'Loki', 'label': 'character', 'score': 0.9962502121925354}, {'start': 122, 'end': 132, 'text': 'alien army', 'label': '', 'score': 0.525113582611084}, {'start': 148, 'end': 156, 'text': 'humanity', 'label': 'location', 'score': 0.4054058790206909}]"
78,Inglourious Basterds,"Adventure,Drama,War","In Nazi-occupied France during World War II, a plan to assassinate Nazi leaders by a group of Jewish U.S. soldiers coincides with a theatre owner's vengeful plans for the same.",Quentin Tarantino,"Brad Pitt, Diane Kruger, Eli Roth,Mélanie Laurent",2009,153,8.3,959065,120.52,69,"[{'start': 3, 'end': 23, 'text': 'Nazi-occupied France', 'label': 'location', 'score': 0.9777075052261353}, {'start': 67, 'end': 79, 'text': 'Nazi leaders', 'label': 'person', 'score': 0.9112507700920105}, {'start': 94, 'end': 114, 'text': 'Jewish U.S. soldiers', 'label': 'person', 'score': 0.8223329186439514}, {'start': 132, 'end': 145, 'text': 'theatre owner', 'label': 'person', 'score': 0.9343565106391907}]"
79,Pirates of the Caribbean: Dead Man's Chest,"Action,Adventure,Fantasy","Jack Sparrow races to recover the heart of Davy Jones to avoid enslaving his soul to Jones' service, as other friends and foes seek the heart for their own agenda as well.",Gore Verbinski,"Johnny Depp, Orlando Bloom, Keira Knightley, Jack Davenport",2006,151,7.3,552027,423.03,53,"[{'start': 0, 'end': 12, 'text': 'Jack Sparrow', 'label': 'character', 'score': 0.5146197080612183}, {'start': 43, 'end': 53, 'text': 'Davy Jones', 'label': 'person', 'score': 0.9827457666397095}, {'start': 85, 'end': 90, 'text': 'Jones', 'label': 'person', 'score': 0.4799237847328186}]"
80,Ghostbusters,"Action,Comedy,Fantasy","Following a ghost invasion of Manhattan, paranormal enthusiasts Erin Gilbert and Abby Yates, nuclear engineer Jillian Holtzmann, and subway worker Patty Tolan band together to stop the otherworldly threat.",Paul Feig,"Melissa McCarthy, Kristen Wiig, Kate McKinnon, Leslie Jones",2016,116,5.3,147717,128.34,60,"[{'start': 30, 'end': 39, 'text': 'Manhattan', 'label': 'location', 'score': 0.9944451451301575}, {'start': 64, 'end': 76, 'text': 'Erin Gilbert', 'label': 'person', 'score': 0.991459846496582}, {'start': 81, 'end': 91, 'text': 'Abby Yates', 'label': 'person', 'score': 0.9905850291252136}, {'start': 110, 'end': 127, 'text': 'Jillian Holtzmann', 'label': 'person', 'score': 0.9912583231925964}, {'start': 147, 'end': 158, 'text': 'Patty Tolan', 'label': 'person', 'score': 0.9862566590309143}]"
81,Inception,"Action,Adventure,Sci-Fi","A thief, who steals corporate secrets through use of dream-sharing technology, is given the inverse task of planting an idea into the mind of a CEO.",Christopher Nolan,"Leonardo DiCaprio, Joseph Gordon-Levitt, Ellen Page, Ken Watanabe",2010,148,8.8,1583625,292.57,74,"[{'start': 0, 'end': 1, 'text': 'A', 'label': 'person', 'score': 0.5232434272766113}, {'start': 2, 'end': 7, 'text': 'thief', 'label': 'character', 'score': 0.8231370449066162}, {'start': 144, 'end': 147, 'text': 'CEO', 'label': 'person', 'score': 0.9688488245010376}]"
82,Captain Fantastic,"Comedy,Drama","In the forests of the Pacific Northwest, a father devoted to raising his six kids with a rigorous physical and intellectual education is forced to leave his paradise and enter the world, challenging his idea of what it means to be a parent.",Matt Ross,"Viggo Mortensen, George MacKay, Samantha Isler,Annalise Basso",2016,118,7.9,105081,5.88,72,"[{'start': 22, 'end': 39, 'text': 'Pacific Northwest', 'label': 'location', 'score': 0.9951253533363342}, {'start': 43, 'end': 49, 'text': 'father', 'label': 'person', 'score': 0.9724830985069275}, {'start': 73, 'end': 81, 'text': 'six kids', 'label': 'person', 'score': 0.5792644023895264}, {'start': 180, 'end': 185, 'text': 'world', 'label': 'location', 'score': 0.40754958987236023}, {'start': 233, 'end': 239, 'text': 'parent', 'label': 'person', 'score': 0.7190936207771301}]"
83,The Wolf of Wall Street,"Biography,Comedy,Crime","Based on the true story of Jordan Belfort, from his rise to a wealthy stock-broker living the high life to his fall involving crime, corruption and the federal government.",Martin Scorsese,"Leonardo DiCaprio, Jonah Hill, Margot Robbie,Matthew McConaughey",2013,180,8.2,865134,116.87,75,"[{'start': 27, 'end': 41, 'text': 'Jordan Belfort', 'label': 'person', 'score': 0.9846912026405334}, {'start': 152, 'end': 170, 'text': 'federal government', 'label': 'location', 'score': 0.7510787844657898}]"
84,Gone Girl,"Crime,Drama,Mystery","With his wife's disappearance having become the focus of an intense media circus, a man sees the spotlight turned on him when it's suspected that he may not be innocent.",David Fincher,"Ben Affleck, Rosamund Pike, Neil Patrick Harris,Tyler Perry",2014,149,8.1,636243,167.74,79,"[{'start': 0, 'end': 4, 'text': 'With', 'label': 'person', 'score': 0.4520743191242218}, {'start': 9, 'end': 13, 'text': 'wife', 'label': 'person', 'score': 0.9007655382156372}, {'start': 68, 'end': 80, 'text': 'media circus', 'label': 'location', 'score': 0.4985864758491516}, {'start': 84, 'end': 87, 'text': 'man', 'label': 'person', 'score': 0.9356613159179688}]"
85,Furious Seven,"Action,Crime,Thriller",Deckard Shaw seeks revenge against Dominic Toretto and his family for his comatose brother.,James Wan,"Vin Diesel, Paul Walker, Dwayne Johnson, Jason Statham",2015,137,7.2,301249,350.03,67,"[{'start': 0, 'end': 12, 'text': 'Deckard Shaw', 'label': 'character', 'score': 0.5796460509300232}, {'start': 35, 'end': 50, 'text': 'Dominic Toretto', 'label': 'person', 'score': 0.8882938027381897}]"
86,Jurassic World,"Action,Adventure,Sci-Fi","A new theme park, built on the original site of Jurassic Park, creates a genetically modified hybrid dinosaur, which escapes containment and goes on a killing spree.",Colin Trevorrow,"Chris Pratt, Bryce Dallas Howard, Ty Simpkins,Judy Greer",2015,124,7.0,455169,652.18,59,"[{'start': 0, 'end': 16, 'text': 'A new theme park', 'label': 'location', 'score': 0.4502316415309906}, {'start': 48, 'end': 61, 'text': 'Jurassic Park', 'label': 'location', 'score': 0.9580839276313782}]"
87,Live by Night,"Crime,Drama","A group of Boston-bred gangsters set up shop in balmy Florida during the Prohibition era, facing off against the competition and the Ku Klux Klan.",Ben Affleck,"Ben Affleck, Elle Fanning, Brendan Gleeson, Chris Messina",2016,129,6.4,27869,10.38,49,"[{'start': 11, 'end': 32, 'text': 'Boston-bred gangsters', 'label': 'person', 'score': 0.5927199125289917}, {'start': 54, 'end': 61, 'text': 'Florida', 'label': 'location', 'score': 0.9943782687187195}, {'start': 133, 'end': 145, 'text': 'Ku Klux Klan', 'label': '', 'score': 0.5263053774833679}]"
88,Avatar,"Action,Adventure,Fantasy",A paraplegic marine dispatched to the moon Pandora on a unique mission becomes torn between following his orders and protecting the world he feels is his home.,James Cameron,"Sam Worthington, Zoe Saldana, Sigourney Weaver, Michelle Rodriguez",2009,162,7.8,935408,760.51,83,"[{'start': 2, 'end': 19, 'text': 'paraplegic marine', 'label': 'character', 'score': 0.8664516806602478}, {'start': 43, 'end': 50, 'text': 'Pandora', 'label': 'location', 'score': 0.9935152530670166}]"
89,The Hateful Eight,"Crime,Drama,Mystery","In the dead of a Wyoming winter, a bounty hunter and his prisoner find shelter in a cabin currently inhabited by a collection of nefarious characters.",Quentin Tarantino,"Samuel L. Jackson, Kurt Russell, Jennifer Jason Leigh, Walton Goggins",2015,187,7.8,341170,54.12,68,"[{'start': 17, 'end': 24, 'text': 'Wyoming', 'label': 'location', 'score': 0.9953317046165466}, {'start': 35, 'end': 48, 'text': 'bounty hunter', 'label': 'person', 'score': 0.955043375492096}, {'start': 57, 'end': 65, 'text': 'prisoner', 'label': 'person', 'score': 0.8999956250190735}, {'start': 84, 'end': 89, 'text': 'cabin', 'label': 'location', 'score': 0.7858065962791443}, {'start': 129, 'end': 149, 'text': 'nefarious characters', 'label': 'character', 'score': 0.9306349754333496}]"
90,The Accountant,"Action,Crime,Drama","As a math savant uncooks the books for a new client, the Treasury Department closes in on his activities and the body count starts to rise.",Gavin O'Connor,"Ben Affleck, Anna Kendrick, J.K. Simmons, Jon Bernthal",2016,128,7.4,162122,86.2,51,"[{'start': 5, 'end': 16, 'text': 'math savant', 'label': 'person', 'score': 0.8766621947288513}, {'start': 41, 'end': 51, 'text': 'new client', 'label': 'person', 'score': 0.5822021961212158}, {'start': 57, 'end': 76, 'text': 'Treasury Department', 'label': 'location', 'score': 0.9810172915458679}]"
91,Prisoners,"Crime,Drama,Mystery","When Keller Dover's daughter and her friend go missing, he takes matters into his own hands as the police pursue multiple leads and the pressure mounts.",Denis Villeneuve,"Hugh Jackman, Jake Gyllenhaal, Viola Davis,Melissa Leo",2013,153,8.1,431185,60.96,74,"[{'start': 0, 'end': 4, 'text': 'When', 'label': 'person', 'score': 0.4244159162044525}, {'start': 5, 'end': 17, 'text': 'Keller Dover', 'label': 'character', 'score': 0.9646700620651245}]"
92,Warcraft,"Action,Adventure,Fantasy","As an Orc horde invades the planet Azeroth using a magic portal, a few human heroes and dissenting Orcs must attempt to stop the true evil behind this war.",Duncan Jones,"Travis Fimmel, Paula Patton, Ben Foster, Dominic Cooper",2016,123,7.0,187547,47.17,32,"[{'start': 6, 'end': 15, 'text': 'Orc horde', 'label': 'location', 'score': 0.49116137623786926}, {'start': 35, 'end': 42, 'text': 'Azeroth', 'label': 'location', 'score': 0.9858124256134033}, {'start': 71, 'end': 83, 'text': 'human heroes', 'label': 'character', 'score': 0.7220969200134277}, {'start': 88, 'end': 103, 'text': 'dissenting Orcs', 'label': 'character', 'score': 0.5026500821113586}]"
93,The Help,Drama,"An aspiring author during the civil rights movement of the 1960s decides to write a book detailing the African American maids' point of view on the white families for which they work, and the hardships they go through on a daily basis.",Tate Taylor,"Emma Stone, Viola Davis, Octavia Spencer, Bryce Dallas Howard",2011,146,8.1,342429,169.71,62,"[{'start': 0, 'end': 18, 'text': 'An aspiring author', 'label': 'book', 'score': 0.614433765411377}, {'start': 84, 'end': 88, 'text': 'book', 'label': 'book', 'score': 0.5048645734786987}, {'start': 103, 'end': 125, 'text': 'African American maids', 'label': 'person', 'score': 0.6442196369171143}, {'start': 148, 'end': 162, 'text': 'white families', 'label': 'location', 'score': 0.594567596912384}]"
94,War Dogs,"Comedy,Crime,Drama","Based on the true story of two young men, David Packouz and Efraim Diveroli, who won a $300 million contract from the Pentagon to arm America's allies in Afghanistan.",Todd Phillips,"Jonah Hill, Miles Teller, Steve Lantz, Gregg Weiner",2016,114,7.1,106463,43.02,57,"[{'start': 42, 'end': 55, 'text': 'David Packouz', 'label': 'person', 'score': 0.9910215735435486}, {'start': 60, 'end': 75, 'text': 'Efraim Diveroli', 'label': 'person', 'score': 0.9922552108764648}, {'start': 118, 'end': 126, 'text': 'Pentagon', 'label': 'location', 'score': 0.4664651155471802}, {'start': 134, 'end': 141, 'text': 'America', 'label': 'location', 'score': 0.757649838924408}, {'start': 154, 'end': 165, 'text': 'Afghanistan', 'label': 'location', 'score': 0.9512442946434021}]"
95,Avengers: Age of Ultron,"Action,Adventure,Sci-Fi","When Tony Stark and Bruce Banner try to jump-start a dormant peacekeeping program called Ultron, things go horribly wrong and it's up to Earth's mightiest heroes to stop the villainous Ultron from enacting his terrible plan.",Joss Whedon,"Robert Downey Jr., Chris Evans, Mark Ruffalo, Chris Hemsworth",2015,141,7.4,516895,458.99,66,"[{'start': 5, 'end': 15, 'text': 'Tony Stark', 'label': 'character', 'score': 0.9817892909049988}, {'start': 20, 'end': 32, 'text': 'Bruce Banner', 'label': 'character', 'score': 0.9916763305664062}, {'start': 89, 'end': 95, 'text': 'Ultron', 'label': 'character', 'score': 0.9874788522720337}, {'start': 137, 'end': 142, 'text': 'Earth', 'label': 'location', 'score': 0.9405564665794373}, {'start': 185, 'end': 191, 'text': 'Ultron', 'label': 'character', 'score': 0.9932973980903625}]"
96,The Nice Guys,"Action,Comedy,Crime","In 1970s Los Angeles, a mismatched pair of private eyes investigate a missing girl and the mysterious death of a porn star.",Shane Black,"Russell Crowe, Ryan Gosling, Angourie Rice, Matt Bomer",2016,116,7.4,175067,36.25,70,"[{'start': 9, 'end': 20, 'text': 'Los Angeles', 'label': 'location', 'score': 0.9882423281669617}, {'start': 24, 'end': 55, 'text': 'mismatched pair of private eyes', 'label': 'character', 'score': 0.7983084321022034}, {'start': 70, 'end': 82, 'text': 'missing girl', 'label': 'person', 'score': 0.922576367855072}, {'start': 113, 'end': 122, 'text': 'porn star', 'label': 'person', 'score': 0.9180553555488586}]"
97,Kimi no na wa,"Animation,Drama,Fantasy","Two strangers find themselves linked in a bizarre way. When a connection forms, will distance be the only thing to keep them apart?",Makoto Shinkai,"Ryûnosuke Kamiki, Mone Kamishiraishi, Ryô Narita, Aoi Yuki",2016,106,8.6,34110,4.68,79,"[{'start': 0, 'end': 13, 'text': 'Two strangers', 'label': 'person', 'score': 0.6034823060035706}]"
98,The Void,"Horror,Mystery,Sci-Fi","Shortly after delivering a patient to an understaffed hospital, a police officer experiences strange and violent occurrences seemingly linked to a group of mysterious hooded figures.",Jeremy Gillespie,"Aaron Poole, Kenneth Welsh,Daniel Fathers, Kathleen Munroe",2016,90,5.8,9247,0.15,62,"[{'start': 27, 'end': 34, 'text': 'patient', 'label': 'person', 'score': 0.7709416151046753}, {'start': 54, 'end': 62, 'text': 'hospital', 'label': 'location', 'score': 0.9160355925559998}, {'start': 66, 'end': 80, 'text': 'police officer', 'label': 'person', 'score': 0.9637536406517029}, {'start': 167, 'end': 181, 'text': 'hooded figures', 'label': 'location', 'score': 0.4913475811481476}]"
99,Personal Shopper,"Drama,Mystery,Thriller",A personal shopper in Paris refuses to leave the city until she makes contact with her twin brother who previously died there. Her life becomes more complicated when a mysterious person contacts her via text message.,Olivier Assayas,"Kristen Stewart, Lars Eidinger, Sigrid Bouaziz,Anders Danielsen Lie",2016,105,6.3,10181,1.29,77,"[{'start': 0, 'end': 1, 'text': 'A', 'label': 'person', 'score': 0.44116175174713135}, {'start': 2, 'end': 18, 'text': 'personal shopper', 'label': 'person', 'score': 0.6113795042037964}, {'start': 22, 'end': 27, 'text': 'Paris', 'label': 'location', 'score': 0.9989396929740906}, {'start': 87, 'end': 99, 'text': 'twin brother', 'label': 'person', 'score': 0.8090435862541199}, {'start': 168, 'end': 185, 'text': 'mysterious person', 'label': 'person', 'score': 0.8737199306488037}]"
100,The Departed,"Crime,Drama,Thriller",An undercover cop and a mole in the police attempt to identify each other while infiltrating an Irish gang in South Boston.,Martin Scorsese,"Leonardo DiCaprio, Matt Damon, Jack Nicholson, Mark Wahlberg",2006,151,8.5,937414,132.37,85,"[{'start': 3, 'end': 17, 'text': 'undercover cop', 'label': 'person', 'score': 0.940721333026886}, {'start': 24, 'end': 42, 'text': 'mole in the police', 'label': 'person', 'score': 0.7848033308982849}, {'start': 96, 'end': 106, 'text': 'Irish gang', 'label': 'location', 'score': 0.6122705936431885}, {'start': 110, 'end': 122, 'text': 'South Boston', 'label': 'location', 'score': 0.9916051626205444}]"
101,Legend,"Biography,Crime,Drama",Identical twin gangsters Ronald and Reginald Kray terrorize London during the 1960s.,Brian Helgeland,"Tom Hardy, Emily Browning, Taron Egerton, Paul Anderson",2015,132,7.0,108836,1.87,55,"[{'start': 25, 'end': 31, 'text': 'Ronald', 'label': 'person', 'score': 0.6405001878738403}, {'start': 36, 'end': 49, 'text': 'Reginald Kray', 'label': 'person', 'score': 0.9822017550468445}, {'start': 60, 'end': 66, 'text': 'London', 'label': 'location', 'score': 0.9921384453773499}]"
102,Thor,"Action,Adventure,Fantasy","The powerful but arrogant god Thor is cast out of Asgard to live amongst humans in Midgard (Earth), where he soon becomes one of their finest defenders.",Kenneth Branagh,"Chris Hemsworth, Anthony Hopkins, Natalie Portman, Tom Hiddleston",2011,115,7.0,570814,181.02,57,"[{'start': 30, 'end': 34, 'text': 'Thor', 'label': 'character', 'score': 0.9958653450012207}, {'start': 50, 'end': 56, 'text': 'Asgard', 'label': 'location', 'score': 0.9921348094940186}, {'start': 83, 'end': 90, 'text': 'Midgard', 'label': 'location', 'score': 0.9924066662788391}, {'start': 92, 'end': 97, 'text': 'Earth', 'label': 'location', 'score': 0.9425503015518188}]"
103,The Martian,"Adventure,Drama,Sci-Fi","An astronaut becomes stranded on Mars after his team assume him dead, and must rely on his ingenuity to find a way to signal to Earth that he is alive.",Ridley Scott,"Matt Damon, Jessica Chastain, Kristen Wiig, Kate Mara",2015,144,8.0,556097,228.43,80,"[{'start': 0, 'end': 2, 'text': 'An', 'label': 'person', 'score': 0.5680252909660339}, {'start': 3, 'end': 12, 'text': 'astronaut', 'label': 'person', 'score': 0.9062030911445618}, {'start': 33, 'end': 37, 'text': 'Mars', 'label': 'location', 'score': 0.997934103012085}, {'start': 128, 'end': 133, 'text': 'Earth', 'label': 'location', 'score': 0.9959155917167664}]"
104,Contratiempo,"Crime,Mystery,Thriller",A young businessman faces a lawyer trying to prove his innocence by the assassination of his lover.,Oriol Paulo,"Mario Casas, Ana Wagener, José Coronado, Bárbara Lennie",2016,106,7.9,7204,0.0,51,"[{'start': 0, 'end': 19, 'text': 'A young businessman', 'label': 'person', 'score': 0.844245970249176}, {'start': 28, 'end': 34, 'text': 'lawyer', 'label': 'person', 'score': 0.9392619132995605}, {'start': 93, 'end': 98, 'text': 'lover', 'label': 'person', 'score': 0.8311269283294678}]"
105,The Man from U.N.C.L.E.,"Action,Adventure,Comedy","In the early 1960s, CIA agent Napoleon Solo and KGB operative Illya Kuryakin participate in a joint mission against a mysterious criminal organization, which is working to proliferate nuclear weapons.",Guy Ritchie,"Henry Cavill, Armie Hammer, Alicia Vikander, Elizabeth Debicki",2015,116,7.3,202973,45.43,56,"[{'start': 30, 'end': 43, 'text': 'Napoleon Solo', 'label': 'person', 'score': 0.9880709648132324}, {'start': 62, 'end': 76, 'text': 'Illya Kuryakin', 'label': 'person', 'score': 0.9900863766670227}]"
106,Hell or High Water,"Crime,Drama,Thriller",A divorced father and his ex-con older brother resort to a desperate scheme in order to save their family's ranch in West Texas.,David Mackenzie,"Chris Pine, Ben Foster, Jeff Bridges, Gil Birmingham",2016,102,7.7,115546,26.86,88,"[{'start': 2, 'end': 17, 'text': 'divorced father', 'label': 'person', 'score': 0.8932388424873352}, {'start': 26, 'end': 46, 'text': 'ex-con older brother', 'label': 'character', 'score': 0.8604024648666382}, {'start': 117, 'end': 127, 'text': 'West Texas', 'label': 'location', 'score': 0.9891949892044067}]"
107,The Comedian,Comedy,A look at the life of an aging insult comic named Jack Burke.,Taylor Hackford,"Robert De Niro, Leslie Mann, Danny DeVito, Edie Falco",2016,120,5.4,1954,1.66,40,"[{'start': 50, 'end': 60, 'text': 'Jack Burke', 'label': 'character', 'score': 0.9762696623802185}]"
108,The Legend of Tarzan,"Action,Adventure,Drama","Tarzan, having acclimated to life in London, is called back to his former home in the jungle to investigate the activities at a mining encampment.",David Yates,"Alexander Skarsgård, Rory J. Saper, Christian Stevens, Christoph Waltz",2016,110,6.3,117590,126.59,44,"[{'start': 37, 'end': 43, 'text': 'London', 'label': 'location', 'score': 0.990385890007019}, {'start': 86, 'end': 92, 'text': 'jungle', 'label': 'location', 'score': 0.9180535674095154}, {'start': 128, 'end': 145, 'text': 'mining encampment', 'label': 'location', 'score': 0.9346377849578857}]"
109,All We Had,Drama,A mother struggles to make a better life for her daughter.,Katie Holmes,"Eve Lindley, Richard Kind, Mark Consuelos, Katherine Reis",2016,105,5.8,1004,0.0,48,"[{'start': 0, 'end': 1, 'text': 'A', 'label': 'person', 'score': 0.7125710844993591}, {'start': 2, 'end': 8, 'text': 'mother', 'label': 'person', 'score': 0.9808268547058105}, {'start': 49, 'end': 57, 'text': 'daughter', 'label': 'character', 'score': 0.8486291766166687}]"
110,Ex Machina,"Drama,Mystery,Sci-Fi",A young programmer is selected to participate in a ground-breaking experiment in synthetic intelligence by evaluating the human qualities of a breath-taking humanoid A.I.,Alex Garland,"Alicia Vikander, Domhnall Gleeson, Oscar Isaac,Sonoya Mizuno",2014,108,7.7,339797,25.44,78,"[{'start': 8, 'end': 18, 'text': 'programmer', 'label': 'person', 'score': 0.851679265499115}, {'start': 166, 'end': 170, 'text': 'A.I.', 'label': 'character', 'score': 0.7985743284225464}]"
111,The Belko Experiment,"Action,Horror,Thriller","In a twisted social experiment, 80 Americans are locked in their high-rise corporate office in Bogotá, Colombia and ordered by an unknown voice coming from the company's intercom system to participate in a deadly game of kill or be killed.",Greg McLean,"John Gallagher Jr., Tony Goldwyn, Adria Arjona, John C. McGinley",2016,89,6.3,3712,10.16,44,"[{'start': 65, 'end': 91, 'text': 'high-rise corporate office', 'label': 'location', 'score': 0.48350417613983154}, {'start': 95, 'end': 101, 'text': 'Bogotá', 'label': 'location', 'score': 0.9411777257919312}, {'start': 103, 'end': 111, 'text': 'Colombia', 'label': 'location', 'score': 0.9396528601646423}, {'start': 130, 'end': 143, 'text': 'unknown voice', 'label': 'person', 'score': 0.4637743830680847}]"
112,12 Years a Slave,"Biography,Drama,History","In the antebellum United States, Solomon Northup, a free black man from upstate New York, is abducted and sold into slavery.",Steve McQueen,"Chiwetel Ejiofor, Michael Kenneth Williams, Michael Fassbender, Brad Pitt",2013,134,8.1,486338,56.67,96,"[{'start': 18, 'end': 31, 'text': 'United States', 'label': 'location', 'score': 0.7831910848617554}, {'start': 33, 'end': 48, 'text': 'Solomon Northup', 'label': 'person', 'score': 0.9977027773857117}, {'start': 72, 'end': 88, 'text': 'upstate New York', 'label': 'location', 'score': 0.9826885461807251}]"
113,The Bad Batch,"Romance,Sci-Fi",A dystopian love story in a Texas wasteland and set in a community of cannibals.,Ana Lily Amirpour,"Keanu Reeves, Jason Momoa, Jim Carrey, Diego Luna",2016,118,6.1,512,0.0,65,"[{'start': 2, 'end': 22, 'text': 'dystopian love story', 'label': 'book', 'score': 0.6830741167068481}, {'start': 28, 'end': 33, 'text': 'Texas', 'label': 'location', 'score': 0.9363807439804077}, {'start': 57, 'end': 79, 'text': 'community of cannibals', 'label': 'location', 'score': 0.7857789397239685}]"
114,300,"Action,Fantasy,War",King Leonidas of Sparta and a force of 300 men fight the Persians at Thermopylae in 480 B.C.,Zack Snyder,"Gerard Butler, Lena Headey, David Wenham, Dominic West",2006,117,7.7,637104,210.59,52,"[{'start': 0, 'end': 13, 'text': 'King Leonidas', 'label': 'person', 'score': 0.74960857629776}, {'start': 17, 'end': 23, 'text': 'Sparta', 'label': 'location', 'score': 0.9836755394935608}, {'start': 57, 'end': 65, 'text': 'Persians', 'label': 'location', 'score': 0.5299581289291382}, {'start': 69, 'end': 80, 'text': 'Thermopylae', 'label': 'location', 'score': 0.9849207997322083}]"
115,Harry Potter and the Deathly Hallows: Part 2,"Adventure,Drama,Fantasy","Harry, Ron and Hermione search for Voldemort's remaining Horcruxes in their effort to destroy the Dark Lord as the final battle rages on at Hogwarts.",David Yates,"Daniel Radcliffe, Emma Watson, Rupert Grint, Michael Gambon",2011,130,8.1,590595,380.96,87,"[{'start': 0, 'end': 5, 'text': 'Harry', 'label': 'character', 'score': 0.41774141788482666}, {'start': 7, 'end': 10, 'text': 'Ron', 'label': 'character', 'score': 0.9937352538108826}, {'start': 15, 'end': 23, 'text': 'Hermione', 'label': 'character', 'score': 0.9951171875}, {'start': 35, 'end': 44, 'text': 'Voldemort', 'label': 'character', 'score': 0.799900233745575}, {'start': 98, 'end': 107, 'text': 'Dark Lord', 'label': 'character', 'score': 0.4874779284000397}, {'start': 140, 'end': 148, 'text': 'Hogwarts', 'label': 'location', 'score': 0.9913491606712341}]"
116,Office Christmas Party,Comedy,"When his uptight CEO sister threatens to shut down his branch, the branch manager throws an epic Christmas party in order to land a big client and save the day, but the party gets way out of hand...",Josh Gordon,"Jason Bateman, Olivia Munn, T.J. Miller,Jennifer Aniston",2016,105,5.8,30761,54.73,42,"[{'start': 0, 'end': 4, 'text': 'When', 'label': 'person', 'score': 0.4591403603553772}, {'start': 17, 'end': 27, 'text': 'CEO sister', 'label': 'person', 'score': 0.8764426708221436}, {'start': 55, 'end': 61, 'text': 'branch', 'label': 'location', 'score': 0.7628586888313293}, {'start': 67, 'end': 81, 'text': 'branch manager', 'label': 'person', 'score': 0.9324697852134705}, {'start': 132, 'end': 142, 'text': 'big client', 'label': 'person', 'score': 0.7860090732574463}]"
117,The Neon Demon,"Horror,Thriller","When aspiring model Jesse moves to Los Angeles, her youth and vitality are devoured by a group of beauty-obsessed women who will take any means necessary to get what she has.",Nicolas Winding Refn,"Elle Fanning, Christina Hendricks, Keanu Reeves, Karl Glusman",2016,118,6.2,50359,1.33,51,"[{'start': 20, 'end': 25, 'text': 'Jesse', 'label': 'person', 'score': 0.9853492379188538}, {'start': 35, 'end': 46, 'text': 'Los Angeles', 'label': 'location', 'score': 0.9978317618370056}]"
118,Dangal,"Action,Biography,Drama",Former wrestler Mahavir Singh Phogat and his two wrestler daughters struggle towards glory at the Commonwealth Games in the face of societal oppression.,Nitesh Tiwari,"Aamir Khan, Sakshi Tanwar, Fatima Sana Shaikh,Sanya Malhotra",2016,161,8.8,48969,11.15,52,"[{'start': 16, 'end': 36, 'text': 'Mahavir Singh Phogat', 'label': 'person', 'score': 0.9958090782165527}, {'start': 98, 'end': 116, 'text': 'Commonwealth Games', 'label': 'location', 'score': 0.9710018038749695}]"
119,10 Cloverfield Lane,"Drama,Horror,Mystery","After getting in a car accident, a woman is held in a shelter with two men, who claim the outside world is affected by a widespread chemical attack.",Dan Trachtenberg,"John Goodman, Mary Elizabeth Winstead, John Gallagher Jr., Douglas M. Griffin",2016,104,7.2,192968,71.9,76,"[{'start': 35, 'end': 40, 'text': 'woman', 'label': 'person', 'score': 0.9357145428657532}, {'start': 54, 'end': 61, 'text': 'shelter', 'label': 'location', 'score': 0.7098070383071899}, {'start': 67, 'end': 74, 'text': 'two men', 'label': 'person', 'score': 0.7581174969673157}, {'start': 90, 'end': 103, 'text': 'outside world', 'label': 'location', 'score': 0.8462847471237183}]"
120,Finding Dory,"Animation,Adventure,Comedy","The friendly but forgetful blue tang fish, Dory, begins a search for her long-lost parents, and everyone learns a few things about the real meaning of family along the way.",Andrew Stanton,"Ellen DeGeneres, Albert Brooks,Ed O'Neill, Kaitlin Olson",2016,97,7.4,157026,486.29,77,"[{'start': 43, 'end': 47, 'text': 'Dory', 'label': 'character', 'score': 0.9972696900367737}, {'start': 83, 'end': 90, 'text': 'parents', 'label': 'person', 'score': 0.5990854501724243}]"
121,Miss Peregrine's Home for Peculiar Children,"Adventure,Drama,Family","When Jacob discovers clues to a mystery that stretches across time, he finds Miss Peregrine's Home for Peculiar Children. But the danger deepens after he gets to know the residents and learns about their special powers.",Tim Burton,"Eva Green, Asa Butterfield, Samuel L. Jackson, Judi Dench",2016,127,6.7,101058,87.24,57,"[{'start': 0, 'end': 4, 'text': 'When', 'label': 'character', 'score': 0.68535977602005}, {'start': 5, 'end': 10, 'text': 'Jacob', 'label': 'character', 'score': 0.9940540194511414}, {'start': 77, 'end': 91, 'text': 'Miss Peregrine', 'label': 'character', 'score': 0.8264445662498474}, {'start': 94, 'end': 120, 'text': 'Home for Peculiar Children', 'label': 'location', 'score': 0.6422867178916931}]"
122,Divergent,"Adventure,Mystery,Sci-Fi","In a world divided by factions based on virtues, Tris learns she's Divergent and won't fit in. When she discovers a plot to destroy Divergents, Tris and the mysterious Four must find out what makes Divergents dangerous before it's too late.",Neil Burger,"Shailene Woodley, Theo James, Kate Winslet, Jai Courtney",2014,139,6.7,362093,150.83,48,"[{'start': 5, 'end': 10, 'text': 'world', 'label': 'location', 'score': 0.5682784914970398}, {'start': 49, 'end': 53, 'text': 'Tris', 'label': 'character', 'score': 0.9923875331878662}, {'start': 67, 'end': 76, 'text': 'Divergent', 'label': 'book', 'score': 0.5945032238960266}, {'start': 144, 'end': 148, 'text': 'Tris', 'label': 'character', 'score': 0.9932825565338135}, {'start': 168, 'end': 172, 'text': 'Four', 'label': 'character', 'score': 0.9804350137710571}]"
123,Mike and Dave Need Wedding Dates,"Adventure,Comedy,Romance","Two hard-partying brothers place an online ad to find the perfect dates for their sister's Hawaiian wedding. Hoping for a wild getaway, the boys instead find themselves out-hustled by an uncontrollable duo.",Jake Szymanski,"Zac Efron, Adam Devine, Anna Kendrick, Aubrey Plaza",2016,98,6.0,53183,46.01,51,"[{'start': 0, 'end': 26, 'text': 'Two hard-partying brothers', 'label': 'person', 'score': 0.6854784488677979}, {'start': 82, 'end': 88, 'text': 'sister', 'label': 'person', 'score': 0.8557623624801636}, {'start': 91, 'end': 99, 'text': 'Hawaiian', 'label': 'location', 'score': 0.9419358968734741}, {'start': 140, 'end': 144, 'text': 'boys', 'label': 'person', 'score': 0.7083978652954102}, {'start': 187, 'end': 205, 'text': 'uncontrollable duo', 'label': 'character', 'score': 0.7204378843307495}]"
124,Boyka: Undisputed IV,Action,"In the fourth installment of the fighting franchise, Boyka is shooting for the big leagues when an accidental death in the ring makes him question everything he stands for.",Todor Chapkanov,"Scott Adkins, Teodora Duhovnikova, Alon Aboutboul, Julian Vergov",2016,86,7.4,10428,0.0,52,"[{'start': 33, 'end': 51, 'text': 'fighting franchise', 'label': 'movie', 'score': 0.768940269947052}, {'start': 53, 'end': 58, 'text': 'Boyka', 'label': 'character', 'score': 0.9902951717376709}, {'start': 79, 'end': 90, 'text': 'big leagues', 'label': 'location', 'score': 0.8930936455726624}, {'start': 123, 'end': 127, 'text': 'ring', 'label': 'location', 'score': 0.7077712416648865}]"
125,The Dark Knight Rises,"Action,Thriller","Eight years after the Joker's reign of anarchy, the Dark Knight, with the help of the enigmatic Selina, is forced from his imposed exile to save Gotham City, now on the edge of total annihilation, from the brutal guerrilla terrorist Bane.",Christopher Nolan,"Christian Bale, Tom Hardy, Anne Hathaway,Gary Oldman",2012,164,8.5,1222645,448.13,78,"[{'start': 22, 'end': 27, 'text': 'Joker', 'label': 'character', 'score': 0.9357635974884033}, {'start': 52, 'end': 63, 'text': 'Dark Knight', 'label': 'character', 'score': 0.9653914570808411}, {'start': 96, 'end': 102, 'text': 'Selina', 'label': 'character', 'score': 0.9838521480560303}, {'start': 145, 'end': 156, 'text': 'Gotham City', 'label': 'location', 'score': 0.9945200085639954}, {'start': 233, 'end': 237, 'text': 'Bane', 'label': 'character', 'score': 0.9764719605445862}]"
126,The Jungle Book,"Adventure,Drama,Family","After a threat from the tiger Shere Khan forces him to flee the jungle, a man-cub named Mowgli embarks on a journey of self discovery with the help of panther, Bagheera, and free spirited bear, Baloo.",Jon Favreau,"Neel Sethi, Bill Murray, Ben Kingsley, Idris Elba",2016,106,7.5,198243,364.0,77,"[{'start': 30, 'end': 40, 'text': 'Shere Khan', 'label': 'character', 'score': 0.9667732119560242}, {'start': 64, 'end': 70, 'text': 'jungle', 'label': 'location', 'score': 0.5095502138137817}, {'start': 74, 'end': 81, 'text': 'man-cub', 'label': 'character', 'score': 0.4177173376083374}, {'start': 88, 'end': 94, 'text': 'Mowgli', 'label': 'character', 'score': 0.9960371851921082}, {'start': 160, 'end': 168, 'text': 'Bagheera', 'label': 'character', 'score': 0.9961147308349609}, {'start': 194, 'end': 199, 'text': 'Baloo', 'label': 'character', 'score': 0.9956939220428467}]"
127,Transformers: Age of Extinction,"Action,Adventure,Sci-Fi","Autobots must escape sight from a bounty hunter who has taken control of the human serendipity: Unexpectedly, Optimus Prime and his remaining gang turn to a mechanic, his daughter, and her back street racing boyfriend for help.",Michael Bay,"Mark Wahlberg, Nicola Peltz, Jack Reynor, Stanley Tucci",2014,165,5.7,255483,245.43,32,"[{'start': 34, 'end': 47, 'text': 'bounty hunter', 'label': 'person', 'score': 0.8941095471382141}, {'start': 110, 'end': 123, 'text': 'Optimus Prime', 'label': 'character', 'score': 0.9974576830863953}, {'start': 157, 'end': 165, 'text': 'mechanic', 'label': 'person', 'score': 0.9221485257148743}, {'start': 171, 'end': 179, 'text': 'daughter', 'label': 'person', 'score': 0.8080500364303589}, {'start': 189, 'end': 217, 'text': 'back street racing boyfriend', 'label': 'person', 'score': 0.7153399586677551}]"
128,Nerve,"Adventure,Crime,Mystery","A high school senior finds herself immersed in an online game of truth or dare, where her every move starts to become manipulated by an anonymous community of ""watchers.""",Henry Joost,"Emma Roberts, Dave Franco, Emily Meade, Miles Heizer",2016,96,6.6,69651,38.56,58,"[{'start': 2, 'end': 20, 'text': 'high school senior', 'label': 'person', 'score': 0.8700069785118103}, {'start': 50, 'end': 61, 'text': 'online game', 'label': 'location', 'score': 0.5086731314659119}, {'start': 65, 'end': 78, 'text': 'truth or dare', 'label': 'location', 'score': 0.43373408913612366}, {'start': 136, 'end': 155, 'text': 'anonymous community', 'label': 'location', 'score': 0.44381627440452576}, {'start': 160, 'end': 168, 'text': 'watchers', 'label': 'person', 'score': 0.6959870457649231}]"
129,Mamma Mia!,"Comedy,Family,Musical",The story of a bride-to-be trying to find her real father told using hit songs by the popular '70s group ABBA.,Phyllida Lloyd,"Meryl Streep, Pierce Brosnan, Amanda Seyfried,Stellan Skarsgård",2008,108,6.4,153481,143.7,51,"[{'start': 15, 'end': 26, 'text': 'bride-to-be', 'label': 'character', 'score': 0.9315842986106873}, {'start': 51, 'end': 57, 'text': 'father', 'label': 'person', 'score': 0.4560328722000122}, {'start': 105, 'end': 109, 'text': 'ABBA', 'label': 'person', 'score': 0.4363960027694702}]"
130,The Revenant,"Adventure,Drama,Thriller",A frontiersman on a fur trading expedition in the 1820s fights for survival after being mauled by a bear and left for dead by members of his own hunting team.,Alejandro González Iñárritu,"Leonardo DiCaprio, Tom Hardy, Will Poulter, Domhnall Gleeson",2015,156,8.0,499424,183.64,76,"[{'start': 0, 'end': 1, 'text': 'A', 'label': 'person', 'score': 0.5769603252410889}, {'start': 2, 'end': 14, 'text': 'frontiersman', 'label': 'person', 'score': 0.9396141171455383}, {'start': 20, 'end': 42, 'text': 'fur trading expedition', 'label': 'location', 'score': 0.6740450263023376}, {'start': 50, 'end': 55, 'text': '1820s', 'label': 'location', 'score': 0.75284743309021}]"
131,Fences,Drama,"A working-class African-American father tries to raise his family in the 1950s, while coming to terms with the events of his life.",Denzel Washington,"Denzel Washington, Viola Davis, Stephen Henderson, Jovan Adepo",2016,139,7.3,50953,57.64,79,"[{'start': 16, 'end': 32, 'text': 'African-American', 'label': 'person', 'score': 0.8893787860870361}, {'start': 33, 'end': 39, 'text': 'father', 'label': 'person', 'score': 0.7224942445755005}, {'start': 73, 'end': 78, 'text': '1950s', 'label': 'date', 'score': 0.43054619431495667}]"
132,Into the Woods,"Adventure,Comedy,Drama",A witch tasks a childless baker and his wife with procuring magical items from classic fairy tales to reverse the curse put on their family tree.,Rob Marshall,"Anna Kendrick, Meryl Streep, Chris Pine, Emily Blunt",2014,125,6.0,109756,128.0,69,"[{'start': 0, 'end': 1, 'text': 'A', 'label': 'character', 'score': 0.6275399923324585}, {'start': 2, 'end': 7, 'text': 'witch', 'label': 'character', 'score': 0.9665018916130066}, {'start': 26, 'end': 31, 'text': 'baker', 'label': 'character', 'score': 0.8483344316482544}, {'start': 40, 'end': 44, 'text': 'wife', 'label': 'person', 'score': 0.7310368418693542}, {'start': 79, 'end': 98, 'text': 'classic fairy tales', 'label': 'book', 'score': 0.9888716340065002}, {'start': 133, 'end': 144, 'text': 'family tree', 'label': 'location', 'score': 0.5585954785346985}]"
133,The Shallows,"Drama,Horror,Thriller","A mere 200 yards from shore, surfer Nancy is attacked by a great white shark, with her short journey to safety becoming the ultimate contest of wills.",Jaume Collet-Serra,"Blake Lively, Óscar Jaenada, Angelo Josue Lozano Corzo, Brett Cullen",2016,86,6.4,78328,55.12,59,"[{'start': 22, 'end': 27, 'text': 'shore', 'label': 'location', 'score': 0.6537532210350037}, {'start': 36, 'end': 41, 'text': 'Nancy', 'label': 'person', 'score': 0.9721107482910156}, {'start': 59, 'end': 76, 'text': 'great white shark', 'label': 'location', 'score': 0.5904628038406372}]"
134,Whiplash,"Drama,Music",A promising young drummer enrolls at a cut-throat music conservatory where his dreams of greatness are mentored by an instructor who will stop at nothing to realize a student's potential.,Damien Chazelle,"Miles Teller, J.K. Simmons, Melissa Benoist, Paul Reiser",2014,107,8.5,477276,13.09,88,"[{'start': 2, 'end': 25, 'text': 'promising young drummer', 'label': 'person', 'score': 0.7784927487373352}, {'start': 39, 'end': 68, 'text': 'cut-throat music conservatory', 'label': 'location', 'score': 0.9477176666259766}, {'start': 118, 'end': 128, 'text': 'instructor', 'label': 'person', 'score': 0.9681507349014282}, {'start': 167, 'end': 174, 'text': 'student', 'label': 'person', 'score': 0.8648437261581421}]"
135,Furious 6,"Action,Crime,Thriller","Hobbs has Dominic and Brian reassemble their crew to take down a team of mercenaries: Dominic unexpectedly gets convoluted also facing his presumed deceased girlfriend, Letty.",Justin Lin,"Vin Diesel, Paul Walker, Dwayne Johnson, Michelle Rodriguez",2013,130,7.1,318051,238.67,61,"[{'start': 0, 'end': 5, 'text': 'Hobbs', 'label': 'character', 'score': 0.5039849877357483}, {'start': 10, 'end': 17, 'text': 'Dominic', 'label': 'character', 'score': 0.9974258542060852}, {'start': 22, 'end': 27, 'text': 'Brian', 'label': 'character', 'score': 0.9929682612419128}, {'start': 86, 'end': 93, 'text': 'Dominic', 'label': 'character', 'score': 0.9986801743507385}, {'start': 169, 'end': 174, 'text': 'Letty', 'label': 'character', 'score': 0.9909061193466187}]"
136,The Place Beyond the Pines,"Crime,Drama,Thriller","A motorcycle stunt rider turns to robbing banks as a way to provide for his lover and their newborn child, a decision that puts him on a collision course with an ambitious rookie cop navigating a department ruled by a corrupt detective.",Derek Cianfrance,"Ryan Gosling, Bradley Cooper, Eva Mendes,Craig Van Hook",2012,140,7.3,200090,21.38,68,"[{'start': 2, 'end': 24, 'text': 'motorcycle stunt rider', 'label': 'person', 'score': 0.9043626189231873}, {'start': 76, 'end': 81, 'text': 'lover', 'label': 'person', 'score': 0.7651676535606384}, {'start': 92, 'end': 105, 'text': 'newborn child', 'label': 'person', 'score': 0.4776974618434906}, {'start': 172, 'end': 182, 'text': 'rookie cop', 'label': 'person', 'score': 0.8159914016723633}, {'start': 218, 'end': 235, 'text': 'corrupt detective', 'label': 'person', 'score': 0.8967430591583252}]"
137,No Country for Old Men,"Crime,Drama,Thriller",Violence and mayhem ensue after a hunter stumbles upon a drug deal gone wrong and more than two million dollars in cash near the Rio Grande.,Ethan Coen,"Tommy Lee Jones, Javier Bardem, Josh Brolin, Woody Harrelson",2007,122,8.1,660286,74.27,91,"[{'start': 34, 'end': 40, 'text': 'hunter', 'label': 'person', 'score': 0.9017142653465271}, {'start': 129, 'end': 139, 'text': 'Rio Grande', 'label': 'location', 'score': 0.9957939386367798}]"
138,The Great Gatsby,"Drama,Romance","A writer and wall street trader, Nick, finds himself drawn to the past and lifestyle of his millionaire neighbor, Jay Gatsby.",Baz Luhrmann,"Leonardo DiCaprio, Carey Mulligan, Joel Edgerton,Tobey Maguire",2013,143,7.3,386102,144.81,55,"[{'start': 13, 'end': 24, 'text': 'wall street', 'label': 'location', 'score': 0.868903636932373}, {'start': 33, 'end': 37, 'text': 'Nick', 'label': 'character', 'score': 0.9395771026611328}, {'start': 114, 'end': 124, 'text': 'Jay Gatsby', 'label': 'character', 'score': 0.9895600080490112}]"
139,Shutter Island,"Mystery,Thriller","In 1954, a U.S. marshal investigates the disappearance of a murderess who escaped from a hospital for the criminally insane.",Martin Scorsese,"Leonardo DiCaprio, Emily Mortimer, Mark Ruffalo,Ben Kingsley",2010,138,8.1,855604,127.97,63,"[{'start': 3, 'end': 7, 'text': '1954', 'label': 'date', 'score': 0.871135950088501}, {'start': 11, 'end': 15, 'text': 'U.S.', 'label': 'location', 'score': 0.8515377044677734}, {'start': 16, 'end': 23, 'text': 'marshal', 'label': 'person', 'score': 0.7247797846794128}, {'start': 60, 'end': 69, 'text': 'murderess', 'label': 'person', 'score': 0.9709358215332031}, {'start': 89, 'end': 123, 'text': 'hospital for the criminally insane', 'label': 'location', 'score': 0.9130488634109497}]"
140,Brimstone,"Mystery,Thriller,Western","From the moment the new reverend climbs the pulpit, Liz knows she and her family are in great danger.",Martin Koolhoven,"Dakota Fanning, Guy Pearce, Kit Harington,Carice van Houten",2016,148,7.1,13004,0.0,44,"[{'start': 0, 'end': 4, 'text': 'From', 'label': 'person', 'score': 0.40063202381134033}, {'start': 24, 'end': 32, 'text': 'reverend', 'label': 'person', 'score': 0.711495041847229}, {'start': 44, 'end': 50, 'text': 'pulpit', 'label': 'location', 'score': 0.5079455971717834}, {'start': 52, 'end': 55, 'text': 'Liz', 'label': 'character', 'score': 0.9954522252082825}]"
141,Star Trek,"Action,Adventure,Sci-Fi",The brash James T. Kirk tries to live up to his father's legacy with Mr. Spock keeping him in check as a vengeful Romulan from the future creates black holes to destroy the Federation one planet at a time.,J.J. Abrams,"Chris Pine, Zachary Quinto, Simon Pegg, Leonard Nimoy",2009,127,8.0,526324,257.7,82,"[{'start': 10, 'end': 23, 'text': 'James T. Kirk', 'label': 'character', 'score': 0.9687682390213013}, {'start': 69, 'end': 78, 'text': 'Mr. Spock', 'label': 'character', 'score': 0.9971011281013489}, {'start': 114, 'end': 121, 'text': 'Romulan', 'label': 'character', 'score': 0.7318520545959473}, {'start': 173, 'end': 183, 'text': 'Federation', 'label': 'location', 'score': 0.6095016002655029}]"
142,Diary of a Wimpy Kid,"Comedy,Family","The adventures of a teenager who is fresh out of elementary and transitions to middle school, where he has to learn the consequences and responsibility to survive the year.",Thor Freudenthal,"Zachary Gordon, Robert Capron, Rachael Harris,Steve Zahn",2010,94,6.2,34184,64.0,56,"[{'start': 20, 'end': 28, 'text': 'teenager', 'label': 'character', 'score': 0.885111391544342}, {'start': 49, 'end': 59, 'text': 'elementary', 'label': 'location', 'score': 0.730226457118988}, {'start': 79, 'end': 92, 'text': 'middle school', 'label': 'location', 'score': 0.9041344523429871}]"
143,The Big Short,"Biography,Comedy,Drama","Four denizens in the world of high-finance predict the credit and housing bubble collapse of the mid-2000s, and decide to take on the big banks for their greed and lack of foresight.",Adam McKay,"Christian Bale, Steve Carell, Ryan Gosling, Brad Pitt",2015,130,7.8,246360,70.24,81,"[{'start': 0, 'end': 13, 'text': 'Four denizens', 'label': 'person', 'score': 0.4710926413536072}, {'start': 21, 'end': 42, 'text': 'world of high-finance', 'label': 'location', 'score': 0.9014189839363098}, {'start': 134, 'end': 143, 'text': 'big banks', 'label': 'location', 'score': 0.7570727467536926}]"
144,Room,Drama,A young boy is raised within the confines of a small shed.,Lenny Abrahamson,"Brie Larson, Jacob Tremblay, Sean Bridgers,Wendy Crewson",2015,118,8.2,224132,14.68,86,"[{'start': 2, 'end': 11, 'text': 'young boy', 'label': 'person', 'score': 0.7414305210113525}, {'start': 47, 'end': 57, 'text': 'small shed', 'label': 'location', 'score': 0.7911968231201172}]"
145,Django Unchained,"Drama,Western","With the help of a German bounty hunter , a freed slave sets out to rescue his wife from a brutal Mississippi plantation owner.",Quentin Tarantino,"Jamie Foxx, Christoph Waltz, Leonardo DiCaprio,Kerry Washington",2012,165,8.4,1039115,162.8,81,"[{'start': 19, 'end': 39, 'text': 'German bounty hunter', 'label': 'person', 'score': 0.8703827261924744}, {'start': 44, 'end': 55, 'text': 'freed slave', 'label': 'character', 'score': 0.8894052505493164}, {'start': 79, 'end': 83, 'text': 'wife', 'label': 'person', 'score': 0.40575408935546875}, {'start': 98, 'end': 109, 'text': 'Mississippi', 'label': 'location', 'score': 0.9771795868873596}, {'start': 110, 'end': 126, 'text': 'plantation owner', 'label': 'person', 'score': 0.8335526585578918}]"
146,Ah-ga-ssi,"Drama,Mystery,Romance","A woman is hired as a handmaiden to a Japanese heiress, but secretly she is involved in a plot to defraud her.",Chan-wook Park,"Min-hee Kim, Jung-woo Ha, Jin-woong Jo, So-ri Moon",2016,144,8.1,33418,2.01,84,"[{'start': 0, 'end': 1, 'text': 'A', 'label': 'person', 'score': 0.6563060283660889}, {'start': 2, 'end': 7, 'text': 'woman', 'label': 'person', 'score': 0.9262502789497375}, {'start': 38, 'end': 54, 'text': 'Japanese heiress', 'label': 'person', 'score': 0.9448519349098206}]"
147,The Edge of Seventeen,"Comedy,Drama","High-school life gets even more unbearable for Nadine when her best friend, Krista, starts dating her older brother.",Kelly Fremon Craig,"Hailee Steinfeld, Haley Lu Richardson, Blake Jenner, Kyra Sedgwick",2016,104,7.4,47694,14.26,77,"[{'start': 47, 'end': 53, 'text': 'Nadine', 'label': 'person', 'score': 0.994510293006897}, {'start': 76, 'end': 82, 'text': 'Krista', 'label': 'person', 'score': 0.9917534589767456}]"
148,Watchmen,"Action,Drama,Mystery","In 1985 where former superheroes exist, the murder of a colleague sends active vigilante Rorschach into his own sprawling investigation, uncovering something that could completely change the course of history as we know it.",Zack Snyder,"Jackie Earle Haley, Patrick Wilson, Carla Gugino,Malin Akerman",2009,162,7.6,410249,107.5,56,"[{'start': 0, 'end': 2, 'text': 'In', 'label': '', 'score': 0.4859640300273895}, {'start': 3, 'end': 7, 'text': '1985', 'label': 'date', 'score': 0.9356812834739685}, {'start': 56, 'end': 65, 'text': 'colleague', 'label': 'person', 'score': 0.4551551640033722}, {'start': 89, 'end': 98, 'text': 'Rorschach', 'label': 'character', 'score': 0.9973118305206299}]"
149,Superbad,Comedy,Two co-dependent high school seniors are forced to deal with separation anxiety after their plan to stage a booze-soaked party goes awry.,Greg Mottola,"Michael Cera, Jonah Hill, Christopher Mintz-Plasse, Bill Hader",2007,113,7.6,442082,121.46,76,"[{'start': 17, 'end': 28, 'text': 'high school', 'label': 'location', 'score': 0.5764210224151611}]"
150,Inferno,"Action,Adventure,Crime","When Robert Langdon wakes up in an Italian hospital with amnesia, he teams up with Dr. Sienna Brooks, and together they must race across Europe against the clock to foil a deadly global plot.",Ron Howard,"Tom Hanks, Felicity Jones, Irrfan Khan, Ben Foster",2016,121,6.2,97623,34.26,42,"[{'start': 5, 'end': 19, 'text': 'Robert Langdon', 'label': 'character', 'score': 0.9885950684547424}, {'start': 35, 'end': 51, 'text': 'Italian hospital', 'label': 'location', 'score': 0.8597107529640198}, {'start': 83, 'end': 100, 'text': 'Dr. Sienna Brooks', 'label': 'character', 'score': 0.9682093858718872}, {'start': 137, 'end': 143, 'text': 'Europe', 'label': 'location', 'score': 0.9859846830368042}]"
151,The BFG,"Adventure,Family,Fantasy","An orphan little girl befriends a benevolent giant who takes her to Giant Country, where they attempt to stop the man-eating giants that are invading the human world.",Steven Spielberg,"Mark Rylance, Ruby Barnhill, Penelope Wilton,Jemaine Clement",2016,117,6.4,50853,55.47,66,"[{'start': 10, 'end': 21, 'text': 'little girl', 'label': 'person', 'score': 0.7671251893043518}, {'start': 34, 'end': 50, 'text': 'benevolent giant', 'label': 'character', 'score': 0.9110777378082275}, {'start': 68, 'end': 81, 'text': 'Giant Country', 'label': 'location', 'score': 0.9960349202156067}, {'start': 114, 'end': 131, 'text': 'man-eating giants', 'label': 'character', 'score': 0.650238573551178}, {'start': 154, 'end': 165, 'text': 'human world', 'label': 'location', 'score': 0.8785342574119568}]"
152,The Hunger Games,"Adventure,Sci-Fi,Thriller",Katniss Everdeen voluntarily takes her younger sister's place in the Hunger Games: a televised competition in which two teenagers from each of the twelve Districts of Panem are chosen at random to fight to the death.,Gary Ross,"Jennifer Lawrence, Josh Hutcherson, Liam Hemsworth,Stanley Tucci",2012,142,7.2,735604,408.0,68,"[{'start': 0, 'end': 16, 'text': 'Katniss Everdeen', 'label': 'character', 'score': 0.4797399938106537}, {'start': 69, 'end': 81, 'text': 'Hunger Games', 'label': 'book', 'score': 0.9201188683509827}, {'start': 167, 'end': 172, 'text': 'Panem', 'label': 'location', 'score': 0.922971785068512}]"
153,White Girl,Drama,"Summer, New York City. A college girl falls hard for a guy she just met. After a night of partying goes wrong, she goes to wild extremes to get him back.",Elizabeth Wood,"Morgan Saylor, Brian Marc, Justin Bartha, Adrian Martinez",2016,88,5.8,4299,0.2,65,"[{'start': 8, 'end': 21, 'text': 'New York City', 'label': 'location', 'score': 0.9982792139053345}, {'start': 25, 'end': 37, 'text': 'college girl', 'label': 'person', 'score': 0.9675718545913696}, {'start': 55, 'end': 58, 'text': 'guy', 'label': 'person', 'score': 0.9735381007194519}]"
154,Sicario,"Action,Crime,Drama",An idealistic FBI agent is enlisted by a government task force to aid in the escalating war against drugs at the border area between the U.S. and Mexico.,Denis Villeneuve,"Emily Blunt, Josh Brolin, Benicio Del Toro, Jon Bernthal",2015,121,7.6,243230,46.88,82,"[{'start': 14, 'end': 23, 'text': 'FBI agent', 'label': 'person', 'score': 0.8704373240470886}, {'start': 41, 'end': 62, 'text': 'government task force', 'label': 'location', 'score': 0.4592621624469757}, {'start': 113, 'end': 124, 'text': 'border area', 'label': 'location', 'score': 0.9202009439468384}, {'start': 137, 'end': 141, 'text': 'U.S.', 'label': 'location', 'score': 0.8479586243629456}, {'start': 146, 'end': 152, 'text': 'Mexico', 'label': 'location', 'score': 0.9476304650306702}]"
